♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won’t waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I’m confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 10=
Did you get hurt?
I’m really sorry.
The hem seemed to be caught in something.
Can someone get the first-aid kit here?
Su Xiao! How could you be so careless!
What if you hurt Sis Yan!
I’m alright.
Sis Li Yan.
Fortunately, Sis Yan doesn’t get hurt.
Su Xiao, how come you fell over on flat ground?
Did you do it on purpose?
What do you mean by that?
It’s obvious.
There is nothing on the ground
can get you tripped.
Never mind.
There’re props all over the site,
totally a mess. Just be careful.
Sorry, I was careless. Sorry to trouble you.
Really sorry.
Was it so?
You didn’t mean to hurt Sis Yan
and take her place as the heroine, did you?
=Action=
I really don’t know why I fell over.
You... Why so fierce?
Since some people suspect I did it on purpose.
Why don’t we go check the surveillance videos?
Let’s see what the hell happened.
What... Surveillance videos?
Yep. There is nothing on the ground
that can get me tripped.
Why are you so arrogant!
I can tell what you really are by your face!
Why bother to check that?
Eh, then someone might step on my hem.
Maybe it has shoe prints on it.
Could it really...
Enough, stop it.
Don’t delay the shooting.
Yes. Sis Yan is right. Shooting comes first.
Su Xiao. You need to bandage up the wound.
Okay.
It’s really her!
Thanks for your hard work. Thanks.
I won’t let you off!
Darn it! How could there be such a mean person!
She got me hurt and put the blame on me.
Liu Xuxu was also the candidate
for the supporting role.
She might be ill-affected since you got the role.
Why didn’t you check the surveillance videos?
If she did it,
I could get her removed from the crew.
You don’t have to.
I can take care of it by myself.
I’m not that timid.
What a silly girl.
But I like it. Let me hug you.
When is your next shoot schedule?
Tomorrow,
I need to finish what we haven’t done today.
Speaking of this, lend me some movies.
I wanna learn from them.
What do you want to do?
Put me down! What’re you doing?
Don’t move.
Go to bed early tonight.
Okay.
Su Xiao, why you’re acting like a letting agent?
Be serious, okay?
This is a movie,
not that kind online drama you starred.
This is a good role.
Fingers crossed.
I’ve to find a way.
How long are you going to sleep?
Time for breakfast.
I’m starving now.
Freak! I’m hurt, how to cook for you.
You can cook by yourself if you don’t like.
Help. I can’t focus on the movie
in such awkward atmosphere.
Maybe I should go back to my room.
Wait. Isn’t he going to hold me up, is he?
What’s wrong?
Well... Don’t you have to go to work today?
Lost your job? They found you’re a freak?
I’m doing my work now, as a producer.
You’re working now?
Yep. I’m reading the gossip news.
That’s not work, okay?
Learning what's going on
in the showbiz is part of my job.
Take Liu Xuxu for example.
Do you know she has given the
whole face cosmetic surgery?
Really?
I can tell her nose is fake.
Look, before the surgery.
And this, after the surgery.
Jaw plastic, forehead enhancement,
double-eyelid surgery, open canthus.
That’s right. Also risorius implant.
The whole chain is fake.
You can pinch it next time, maybe it’ll deform.
Are her breasts fake?
You know what, many actresses have fake breasts.
I’m not one of them.
You rascal!
What’re you doing! You freak!
Sorry. I touched it by accident. I didn’t mean that.
You bastard! Get out of my face!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don’t you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪