♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode11=
Xiao Jian! This liar! Freak!
He even said he wouldn't have interest in me!
I'm pissed off!
Damn it! So embarrassing! Oh, no!
We'll meet tomorrow! Oh, no! What to do?
Oh, my! He is coming upstairs!
He is here!
You bastard! Liar! Freak! Don't come over here!
I know I'm in good shape, yet you can't molest me!
Those lines marked in red, what's wrong?
I couldn't finish that scene well.
Take me as Liu Xuxu, and hit on me.
No, I refuse!
Aren't you a professional actress?
Okay, as you wish.
This lady, you're fair...
That's like a yob trying to chat up.
I told you I couldn't get the feeling!
What... are you doing?
This lady, you're fair
and pretty.
What a pity to be a courtesan here.
Would you like to go on a carefree journey with me?
I wouldn't mind even if your boobs were fake.
I've told you...
Keep going.
What nice scenery here.
Yes.
Glinting lake and the petals falling like snow.
Childe, you're quite of elegance.
The scenery is at its best at this time.
But I'm not here for the scenery.
So you're also a worldling aimed at bounty.
You got me wrong. I meant I'm here for beauty.
This lady, you're fair
and pretty. What a pity to be a courtesan here.
Would you like to go on a carefree journey with me?
I'm flattered.
I want nothing more but you this life.
Cut! Ok.
Su Xiao. Well done.
Liu Xuxu, what's wrong with you?
Relax. You showed too much just now.
Er... I'm sorry.
Give Xuxu several close-ups from another angle.
Edit it.
Okay, director.
What happened? She showed completely different.
OMG! Su Xiao is so charming today!
Impressive acting!
I also wanna be chatted up by her!
Fast progress.
You... What the hell made you...
This lady, you're fair.
Throw in the sponge?
No way!
Liu Xuxu. The costume will be torn.
I'm sorry.
Er... Your chin...
She did have plastic surgery.
Yes.
That's all for today's shooting!
Thank you all. See you tomorrow.
=Filming Set=
See you tomorrow.
Well done.
Sis Li Yan.
The scene you reshot today was incredible.
Really? Thank you, sis Li Yan.
Guys! Have a break!
Mr. Li brought some desserts to visit us.
So nice!
You must have had a long day.
Would you like something to eat?
I'd like to eat. But I'm losing weight.
It's quite not easy being an actress.
Well, I feel jolly empty.
Take one then.
Many thanks.
Sis Li, time to go.
Okay, I gotta go.
Don't worry, Mr. Li. Every one of us will work hard.
Okay. It's so exciting.
See you tomorrow then.
Su Xiao, see you.
Okay. Sis Li Yan, see you tomorrow.
Director Xu thinks quite highly of you.
Really? Thank you.
But thanks to you, Liu Xuxu has got a miserable day.
How was the shoot today?
It sucked, okay!
Everyone was around Su Xiao. I'm freaked out!
What's wrong? What made you so mad?
Have a cake and chill out, okay?
Look at me! Do you think I'm in the mood to eat?
All Su Xiao's fault!
She went to the hospital.
Sandy is not here today?
Sis Sandy hasn't arrived yet. I go remove my make-up.
And then call him.
If he got tied up, I can send you back.
We're going in the same direction,
I can give you a lift.
You're making up to Xiaoxiao?
Sis Sandy?
I... I didn't do anything.
Just kidding, Li Xiwei.
Sorry, Xiaoxiao. I'm late.
Well, Xiaoxiao is after your heart?
About work, you can come to me.
Er... Okay. If there's nothing else, I'll be going.
See ya.
Sis Sandy.
What issues the hell do you have with Li Xiwei?
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪