♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 16=
=Frost Cold As Blood
The Eighth Day of Shooting=
Look. It's Su Xiao.
Yes. I can't believe she is such a person.
That's right. Don't know whether it's true or not.
Su Xiao! Su Xiao! Su Xiao.
Director Gao, what's wrong?
Where is Sandy?
He has things to do and comes back tonight.
Oh, no! Damn it!
What the hell happened?
Didn't you see the news online?
I saw it!
They knew that I did the flogging scene in person.
Many netizens praised me.
Not that! This one! Look!
=Supporting actress met privately with
assistant director at night!
What's this!
They said this photo was taken last night,
and you got this role because of
your improper relationship with me!
The truth is you failed to take advantage of me!
Lower your voice, okay!
Why would such news...
Must be her!
Moreover, many members of our crew said
they heard strange sound coming from
the side of your room.
They all think that we two were...
What makes you so joyful!
You wanna die?
Do you want me to help you now?
So... Sorry.
Since last night,
has anyone approached you all of a sudden?
No... Nah.
Nobody came to me, either.
Anyhow, I cannot just bear this insult.
Really?
Liu Xuxu.
Su Xiao? You look spirited.
Did you go have fun this morning?
As expected, you did it.
What are you talking about? I can't get it.
Be quick to clear the air.
Why me?
Neglected it? Fine, hope you won't regret it.
Dear me! I'm so scared.
What can you do to make me regret?
I'd like to see that.
You'll screwed it up if director Xu knows this.
Bye-bye, just go back yourself.
Hey, don't gossip like that, okay?
Do you have any proof?
Yao Mengfang...
Su Xiao.
Sis Li Yan.
Thank you so much for last night.
How delicious the dishes you cooked for me!
Make it plausible.
Really sorry. I knew you got scenes to shoot today.
Yet kept you staying with me till this morning.
Never mind.
Ms. Li. So Ms. Su was with you this morning?
That's it. What's up?
Did you hear that?
Okay, have a break!
Sis Yan, thank you so much.
No big deal. I've been in this trade for long.
I've seen different kinds of crews and people.
Someone stabbed others
in the back in order to get a role.
Also someone tried to steal the show at any coast.
I... I really didn't do that.
I know that. You have Sandy with you.
I believe that you wouldn't do such a thing.
He also told me you're good at cooking.
I'll cook for you next time.
Just do it once. Only once.
I can get the role then.
He saw me. No!
What a shame! It's over.
I'm clear that being an actress is not easy.
However,
it's hard to put on the clothes you take off.
Cherish yourself.
He helped me at the most important moment.
So, I want to help you.
What did you say?
Wasn't I supposed to be the endorser?
He clearly told me that he'd take me to see Mr. Wang.
What? He went back?
Then call him, or go to his company!
I can't leave my work, but can't you go?
Cut the crap!
You can go to hell if you can't get it for me!
Shoot.
Easy. A good conscience is not afraid of ghosts.
You know you look like a ghost?
No personal remark, okay?
I've something good for you.
What do you mean?
Would you like to listen to my favorite song?
Take it as a proof of us making peace.
No need. Can you get out of here?
You'll love it, trust me.
I love you so much! Stay with me, okay?
Why do you have this?
Not over yet.
Gimme!
This Mr. Lin is one of our investors, right?
I don't know! No more nonsense!
Maybe your voice is too loud,
maybe the room is not well insulated.
People in other rooms might
not tell whose voice this is.
But I heard it clearly living next door.
It's you who did such a shameless thing.
But you slandered me.
You...
You think you would get away with it?
If you stir up trouble again,
I'll post the audio file online.
Su Xiao, don't you think I can do nothing with you.
Give it a try then.
Just wait and see!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪