♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 08=
It's Sis Sandy.
Time for director Xu's audition is settled.
=The audition starts tomorrow noon.
I'll pick you up there. Get ready=
It's...
Tomorrow?
Audition...
For which scene? The first one?
What should I do? I haven't recited the lines.
Come to my room later.
Didn't you hear what I said?
I have no time to play the cat game with you!
You think I'm kidding?
I have something serious to tell you.
I don't want you to be a stupid cat
and get shamefully nervous just for an audition.
Don't be nervous.
It's just an audition.
By the way,
it's said that the leading
actress is also settled.
She'll come here as well.
Oh, really?
A very famous actress.
Guess, who is she?
Oh, really?
Su Xiao!
You're here!
Su Xiao.
Seeing me here,
don't you feel surprised?
Actually it's director Xu
who told me to come help him.
Unexpected, right?
So,
I'm here.
Doesn't it make you extremely happy?
Sorry, director Gao.
She's just too nervous.
=Frost Cold As Blood
No entry for irrelevant personnel=
Movie Script=
Later,
when director Xiao is here,
let's start the audition from Su Xiao.
I'm the first?
Help. Help.
I can't mess it up.
But,
why that girl
keeps staring at me?
Hi, everyone.
Excuse me.
I'm late.
Hi, director Xu.
That is...
Director Xu in the flesh?
Damn it.
My hands are trembling. What to do?
I don't have time to play this with you now!
I'm gonna meet director Xu tomorrow.
Director Xu?
He likes eating stinky tofu.
Although teased by the crew,
he still sneaks out to eat it.
You got to observe carefully.
If he keeps drinking,
that means he just ate some in private.
Why he has to keep drinking?
Isn't it obvious?
His mouth stinks too much.
Drinking stops him from being
disliked by actors and the crew.
How can that be possible? I don't believe you.
You'll know it by then.
Director Xu is so otherworldly, how could he...
He is!
He keeps drinking!
He really
just ate stinky tofu!
That freak
was telling the truth?
You got to observe carefully.
If he keeps drinking,
that means he just ate some in private.
No trembling now.
Or he said that to save me from being nervous?
How is that possible?
I must over-interpret it.
Okay.
Let's begin the audition.
Director.
What about the leading actress?
She said that she's in a traffic jam.
She's still not here.
I got this!
Don't worry.
With me being your partner,
you'll give full play to your real strength!
Director, what should we do?
It's okay.
We're testing Su Xiao anyway.
Let him be.
Okay.
Ready?
Action.
I didn't expect that you're this kind of person.
Miss, you're really
as beautiful as a flower.
I think even if you're dead,
you can still be a beauty.
Since you're in so much pain,
let me make it easier for you!
In this world,
how could I be the only one
who're made so painful?
Okay.
Done.
Very good. Very good.
Thank you, director.
You still need to mind the details.
But generally, you fit the role.
Su... Su Xiao. Let go.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Li...
Li... Li Yan?
This is our leading actress.
Hi, director.
Hi, everyone.
The leading actress is Li Yan?
Okay.
Everyone is here.
So, let's
continue the audition.
Okay.
The next one is
Liu Xuxu.
Yes, I'm ready.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
=Frost Cold As Blood=
=Starting from 13:30=
=No entry for irrelevant personnel=
=Xiwei Film and Television Limited=
Why didn't you tell me
that the leading actress is Li Yan?
I wanted to.
But you just ignored me.
I didn't expect that
I could work with Li Yan so soon.
Ah, I'm so...
What's up?
That is...
Liu Xuxu.
She's pretty popular lately.
The man next to her
is the investor of this movie.
Li Xiwei.
Long time no see.
Sandy?
How could you be here?
Sis Sandy.
You know each other?
Old friends.
You're back again?
I'm still with Xiao Jian.
This is our company's Su Xiao.
Please take care of her.
Su Xiao?
You stole the supporting role from Xuxu?
How can you say that she stole it?
The director made the decision.
Is that so?
Xiao Jian...
I'm leaving.
Well...
Mr. Li.
I will
try my best to play the role well.
Then I shall
wait and see.
That's what happened?
Really?
Li Yan is really beautiful!
So elegant!
Her face is smaller than that on TV.
So beautiful!
I'm not interested in that.
How about the audition?
Director Xu said that I fit the role well.
But I still need to mind the details.
The scriptwriter also
told me to read the script carefully
to consider the role's inner world.
The scriptwriter?
Called Nanshan?
What's the matter?
Nanshan can't behave himself after drinking.
He even stripteases when he's drunk.
What?
How is that possible?
The scriptwriter looks very literary.
Look at this.
Even women's wear.
Made of chiffon.
My god.
I thought he's refined in manner.
And this...
So unexpected.
This is so...
What's up?
I... Well...
Well...
This time,
Thank... Thank you.
Or I wouldn't have taken this role.
Your favor...
Your favor is beyond words to return.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪