♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 03=
I have no choice
but to turn to Xiao Jian.
I don't know
how it'll be like in the future.
But,
he also said that
he needs me to play a cat to study performance.
Maybe
he was telling the truth.
After all, he's Xiao Jian,
a national-level super star,
a super movie king,
and the nation's idol.
How could he lie to me?
Just to wear a cat outfit,
what's to be ashamed of?
Well,
it's so shameful anyway.
Alright.
Let's call it a day now.
So shameful.
It's so shameful!
You freak!
I think you're just making fun of me!
But it's also a part of the contract.
But the new broker for you is coming soon.
My advice, you need to get changed.
It seems that he's already here.
He... he is?
Now it's okay.
You...
So fast.
Hi, who's there?
Hi, hefty man.
Hi, you're here.
Hello, Jianjian.
Morning.
Hello, baby.
Hell... Hello.
Sorry
to make you come here in person.
No problem. No problem.
I've been idling for years.
It's time to check on the
very important one I'm responsible for, baby.
You're Su Xiao, right?
Just call me Sis Sandy.
From now on,
I'll be your broker.
Sis Sandy is a very excellent broker.
From now on, your work...
You seldom gave me praise.
What's wrong today?
Jianjian, you miss me?
Go away.
What a monster.
Fine.
Well,
what kind of actress Su Xiao wants to be?
Well...
Just like
Li Yan.
She doesn't look like a bad girl.
She's pure
and beautiful.
And she can play the heroine.
Li Yan.
You mean Li Yan?
Stop kidding me.
That's impossible. Impossible.
Why impossible?
Having a dream matters a lot.
How can you mock at others' dream like this?
Jianjian, why do you still hold such a bad habit?
I see.
You think that the heroine is at
a higher level than the female villain.
Right?
Never mind.
Just keep working hard like this
and take Li Yan as your goal.
I've seen two shows of you.
Your performance is meticulous
and right in place.
You're very talented.
Thank you.
Well...
Sis Sandy.
As of today,
I'll spare no effort to support you, honey.
How should I tell it to my brother?
I'm back, brother.
So tired mentally.
Why are you home so late today?
And you look so tired.
Many things happened.
Have you eaten anything?
I've made some soup.
Go to sleep after you drink it.
What's wrong?
It's all because of Xiao Jian, that freak.
Now I have to leave my dearest brother.
What?
Brother.
I'm really sorry.
From tomorrow on,
I have to live in the company's apartment.
Apartment?
Can you take care of it?
Su Da.
Can you give a worried facial expression?
Mr. Song.
You're also here?
I'm not worried enough?
Fine.
If there's anything,
remember to call me right away.
Sorry.
I can't cook for you at home any more.
Don't worry about me.
Take good care of yourself.
Thank you, brother.
I've made the choice.
I got to make it till the end
no matter how hard it is.
Never mind.
Sandy said that he'll help me.
And that freak...
He probably
can be reliable sometimes.
What's going on?
Okay.
She'll try this one next time.
Wait...
It's too fast. I can't catch it!
Alright.
Let's play another one.
Come. Come.
This way. This way.
Come catch this.
Come.
Hurry. Hurry.
Come on.
What on earth am I doing?
It's been days since I signed the contract.
I did nothing serious
but house chores here.
Now I'm just like a baby-sitter.
I quit. I quit!
He may find someone else.
Why should I have to clean up the room,
cook and wash clothes for him every day?
Go find someone else!
=Xiao Jian the Movie King looks after a baby!
What a warm and touching scene!=
Our Jian is so caring!
Ah, I'm so intrigued!
I want to have a child with Jian!
I also want a hug from him!
Xiao Jian please marry me!
When will Jian be a father?
What's that comment?
Who will marry you?
=I'll see it ten times!=
Xiao Jian is my child's father!
=I want to become that baby...=
Our Jian...
During private time...
Basically,
I just read books
surf on the Internet,
and watch some old movies at home.
I really don't have any special hobby.
I think,
roles are just roles.
My private life
is actually very boring.
What the hell?!
Xiao Jian is such a double-dealer!
He's actually a big freak!
Who's a freak?
It hurts. It hurts.
If you want to show cuteness,
put on the cat outfit first.
It hurts so much, my gosh.
And,
did you cook?
What did you say?!
You really take me as a baby-sitter?
I warn you,
Movie King Xiao,
I've gotten many secrets of you.
Your fame will be doomed
if I just put several of them online!
You better not piss me off!
Look how awesome you are.
Do you need me to kiss you, hug you and hold you up?
Shut up!
If you get it,
you should respect me more!
Go post it then.
But,
the audience will believe me,
a national-level movie king,
or you, who specialize in playing villains?
If I say that you hype maliciously
using my popularity,
my fans will diss you to death by then.
=Totally Defeated=
Then your image will be ruined totally.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪