♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 12=
Keep going.
Thanks to Xiao Jian, I could finish my scene well.
I should show my thanks.
However,
that doesn't mean he is a good man in my eyes.
Hmmm... After all, it wasn't in the contract that
he should guide my acting.
Now it feels like I'm owing him a favor.
Anyway, how should I show him my thanks?
Why bother? Just put on this outfit.
No! No! No!
What the hell shall I do?
Xiaoxiao.
Yes?
You've spoken your mind out.
Don't take it so complicated.
Just show your sincerity. Sincerity.
My sincerity...
You're back.
Yes, I...
What... Why you're wearing this?
I just wanted to have a try.
That... You just... Just bought it?
No! Calm down!
I'm a national star.
My image! Image.
Chill out. Chill out.
No way! I can't stay calm!
Have your meal first!
Aren't you afraid you'll choke
to death eating so fast?
The ears feel so amazing!
Oh! There're other colors of this style.
We might as well buy them all.
No!
There's a volar pad on this paw, feels so good!
It couldn't be better if it's of pure wool.
Wow, a tail! So cute!
You freak!
Yeah! Look at me like this! Wonderful!
No! I shouldn't beat him.
I'm dressed up like this to thank him.
Well...
Ah! Since there's a volar pad on fore paw,
the back paw must have it on.
Hurry! Show me your foot, let me scratch it.
What? Scratch my foot!
You damn freak!
Why did I do such a shameful thing!
What a shame!
How could I do such a thing?
That freak! I must have been brainwashed by him.
Was I out of my sense?
Wouldn't it be nice to thank him in a normal way?
What did I do!
You... You... Why're you here?
Why did you suddenly pinch my neck and run away?
‘Cause you... Forget it.
What's wrong? Being angry like a cat?
Well... Yesterday... My scene... I...
As from tomorrow, we'll live on the location.
I forgot this.
So, I can't touch “my cat” these days!
Take all these outfits with you.
You can send me selfies wearing it
in the hotel at night! Or videos!
You're a super freak!
I won't say thanks.
I won't thank the help from such a freak!
Just eat cat food at home these days!
Xiaoxiao, I'm here to pick you up.
Jianjian, Xiaoxiao is about to leave.
Never mind. Sis Sandy. He won't come out. Let's go.
What happened? You quarreled again?
Not my bad.
Okay, we're leaving!
That scene you taught me was done.
Thank you!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪