♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 19=
Su Xiao, smile. Smile.
No. I'm too nervous to smile.
We're here to get you more job offers.
The offer won't come to you
if you're like this.
I've never seen you before, newcomer?
I'm in a good mood today.
Come drink a little with me.
I'll take care of you in the future.
You're drunk, I think.
Leave this to me.
Hey, what are you doing?
Do you know my identity?
Darn it. I do need more chances.
But not this kind of chance.
Su Xiao? Why is she here?
No more preferential treatments?
That means no more good roles, doesn't it?
It seems Mr. Li has taken
a fancy to another actress.
I prefer this quiet place.
What?
Liu Xuxu?
Thanks to you!
My career is totally ruined!
I don't know what happened.
But you gotta know
it's you who ruined your career!
Why put the blame on me?
Bullshitting!
How many dirty things you've done
to snatch roles and resources?
You must be clear about that!
You want me to tell you one by one?
You really think you can get away with
the bad things you've done?
I haven't lost yet.
You've already lost since the day
you got something by trickery.
I don't play dirty tricks like you do.
If you really wanna get even with me,
you can uprightly
compete with me next time.
Just wait and see!
I'll wait for you, Liu Xuxu.
I'm really sorry.
I'm also responsible for
what Liu Xuxu has done.
Mr. Li, that's kind of you.
She only has herself to blame.
Moreover, it's common in the showbiz.
Ah, sorry. I was being so self-righteous.
Really sorry that I influenced your party.
What a funny girl you are.
Er... Where is Sandy?
I like this song very much.
Ah? I see.
Such a rare chance.
May I have a dance with you?
Right here?
Yes, may I?
What's... going on? Why...
What's the situation now?
Alright. Let's get started.
Forget it. Just dance.
You're a good dancer.
I'm flattered.
I'm telling the truth.
How lucky I am to have
such an elegant dancing partner.
Elegant? Me?
Rather elegant.
Moreover, you're of intellectual beauty.
Intellectual beauty!
I've never heard such a praise!
Su Xiao. In my eyes,
your acting skill is like yourself...
Are you alright?
I'm sorry.
Never mind.
Don't know why I suddenly...
Maybe someone is speaking ill of me.
What's going on?
Why didn't answer my call?
I specially chose her spare time at night.
Have some hot water.
Thanks. Thank you, Mr. Li.
Be careful, don't catch a cold.
I'll give it back to you
after I clean your hanky.
Su Xiao, could you please
give me your own phone number
if it's possible?
I wanna talk with you
about something in private.
Gosh! What's going on? Macho boss?
What a cool move! Oh, no!
Feeling of heartbeats!
I'm sorry. You can just
go talk to my broker.
But I just wanna talk to you.
Sandy! Where are you!
I know that. I know.
I'll tell Su Xiao. And call you back.
Oh, Su Xiao.
I saw the clips of
Frost Cold As Blood in advance.
You did quite a good job. Very impressive.
Thank you for your compliment.
It's not so easy to play that role well.
It's set as a cold-blooded villain.
Your performance
have vivified the character.
When the film is released,
your popularity will definitely increase.
And you'll get a steady
flow of film offers.
Hope so.
I have faith in you.
I'm praised!
Easy! Steady myself! Don't get dizzy!
What's wrong? Did I say something wrong?
Not that.
If you can tell me your phone number,
I wanna talk with you in private.
To see if you'd like to cooperate with us.
Maybe it sounds not
so modest for me to say this,
but our company is
one of the best in the industry.
Sure thing.
So, Ms. Su Xiao.
I wonder if I have the honor
to invite you to sign with our company?
Sign with you? You wanna have me join you?
Yes. That's why I specially
invited you here today.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪