♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 02=
Sign with you?
Are you also intended to take advantage of me?
Your appearance holds no appeal to me.
You don't have to say it so directly!
If you refuse,
I'll cancel all the investment
in director Gao at once!
And I'll put the photo of you two
on the headlines of entertainment news
to expose the backstage deal
between director Gao and an actress.
No! Please spare me, boss Xiao!
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
People already find me vicious-looking now.
If I'm involved in that kind of news,
the image of me in audience's mind
will never be able to make a turnaround.
Who will let me play positive roles then?
I...
Fine.
Then tell me, what's the contract about?
Director Gao.
Could you please chill
yourself down outside the room?
Okay. I do feel a little hot now.
How come he runs away so fast.
You...What are you doing?
Okay.
Next I'll tell you about the contract.
Go ahead.
Three articles in the contract.
Firstly,
I'll manage your work in the showbiz exclusively.
I'll introduce to you whatever
resources you want.
I guess,
even if you struggle like this for decades,
you can never get such resources.
Secondly,
you must accept any requirement I ask
to the extent permitted by law.
What requirement?
I'll tell you the details later.
At last,
during the term of the contract,
you also work as my personal assistant.
What?! What did you say?
That's all.
Why should you ask me to be your assistant?
I'm an actress, not a baby-sitter.
To ensure that you can assist me well,
I'll arrange a new dorm for you,
right upstairs my room.
The contract is so weird!
Don't you want to have better
development in the showbiz?
Listen to this again,
I promise that I won't ask for
any illegal requirement.
What should I do?
With better connections from the Movie King,
I'll surely get many jobs better than I have.
But the studio that I'm signing
with has been treating me well.
If I dump them for this reason,
I...
My requirement is,
put this on!
What's this?
When I ask you to wear this,
you must do as I say.
Huh?
Freak!
A sheer freak!
A national-level freak!
What do you say?
A good deal, isn't it?
Are you kidding me?!
Aren't you an idiot?!
Who will sign such a contract?!
Even without you,
my studio will try their best to get jobs for me!
If you spread rumors,
they'll also solve it for me!
Although it's just an unknown studio,
we have team spirit and we'll work really hard!
Who do you think you are?
The Movie King can always get his own way?
Put this on!
You wish.
What a coincidence.
Not take this one?
What... What should I do?
If I take the lift with this
national-level freak alone...
You're not gonna take this one?
Why do I have to avoid this?
What's to be afraid of?
Your face...
So terrible.
About the cat outfit,
you might have misunderstood me.
If I tell you that
it's because I'm gonna shoot a work
about a pet cat turning into a human,
and I need someone to help me figure out
how to imitate and show the cat's body language.
Will you accept to sign with me?
You didn't explain it earlier but now.
You think I'll believe you?
Who knows
if you just made it up to cheat me.
Makes sense.
It's up to you then.
But you're really suitable for this job.
What a pity.
If you want to sign with me,
you may come to me at any time.
Bye-bye.
Are you kidding me?
You freak,
I won't...
I won't sign that damn contract!
=Beauty Studio=
Su Xiao.
Su Xiao, good morning.
What
are you doing?
Sorry, Su Xiao.
Our studio only has one actress, you.
For you, we had to find resources,
sponsors,
and stylists.
But your rewards were so little.
So,
we just settled accounts.
From tomorrow on,
we close down.
What?!
How could it turn into this?
Fine.
Isn't it just a contract?
I'll sign it!
As long as I can still be an actress,
I'll accept whatever requirement!
Wait for me.
You freak!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪