♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 09=
=Frost Cold As Blood
The First Day of Shooting=
The filming finally gets into its stride.
This is my first movie.
Gosh! Such a big-budget movie.
Easy. Easy. I'm not nervous.
Xiaoxiao, you're so cool!
Oh, no! What if I screwed it up?
Don't worry.
You've fully prepared.
Reciting your lines every day.
Practicing your fight actions
and those wire stunts.
You'll make it.
Ready!
Action!
Okay. Cut.
Well done. She's very promising.
Thank you. Please take care of her for my sake then.
Sis Sandy. Did I do it well?
Li Yan?
You did a good job.
Thank you for saying so.
Em... You two...
We've known each other for long.
Sandy has helped me a lot.
Oh, come on! Don't say that.
Ooh, he has never told me about that!
Haven't I?
This is a good role. Fingers crossed.
Okay, thank you.
Never thought I would shoot with Sis Li Yan!
It feels like a dream!
Ow! It hurts.
The hanging wire was too tight.
I got pains all over.
What to do with that?
I brought you my exclusive miracle unguent.
You can apply it later.
Really?
Jianjian also used it.
He said it does work.
Okay. Many thanks.
I clearly remembered I put the
medicine chest here.
Did anyone take it by mistake?
Su Xiao. Just wait and see.
I'm back!
Whew, so tired.
Ah! That freak went on location today.
That is to say...
I can fully enjoy myself here today!
I'm worn out having shot fight
scenes the whole day.
The luxury massage bathtub! I'm coming!
Ow! Ow! It hurts!
It hurts so much!
And now take out the freak's medicine chest.
Apply some of his unguent.
So comfy.
What a beat day today.
Keep going tomorrow.
This fool.
Just some fight scenes,
yet exhausted herself like this.
Looks better.
Good night.
=Frost Cold As Blood
The Second Day of Shooting=
Are you ready?
Director Xu. Yeah, ready.
We're too impatient to wait.
Okay. Let me explain this scene first.
Chu Yixiao who dressed as a boy is lurking here.
She sees a courtesan, and goes to molest her.
So as to get information from her.
Su Xiao. Your show time.
Okay.
Is that okay with you?
Rest assured, director.
I'm not a newcomer doing my first movie.
Well then. Let's get started.
Hope it's done at the first try.
Ready!
Action!
This lady, you're quite fair and pretty.
What a pity to be a courtesan here.
Would you like to go on a carefree journey with me?
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Su Xiao, why you're acting like a letting agent?
You can't act like that.
Sorry! I'm sorry.
Be serious, okay?
This is a movie,
not that kind online drama you starred.
Stop it. One more time.
=TAKE 2=
This lady, you're quite fair and pretty. What a pity...
Cut. You're like selling health products this time.
=TAKE 3=
This lady, you're quite fair and...
Cut. An insurance saleswoman this time.
=TAKE 4=
This lady, you're quite fair...
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Director, really sorry.
I've never hit on a girl.
You've never hit on a girl,
haven't you ever been chatted up by a man?
Yes. No one dares to chat up me as I look termagant.
Forget it. Change the next scene.
Su Xiao, go get yourself fully prepared.
Feel your role thoroughly. Don't waste our time.
I'm terribly sorry, director!
You really can't bear the supporting
role for your first movie.
I still haven't thoroughly grasp the script.
Gotta borrow some classic movies from
movie king Xiao.
What happened?
It looks like someone fell over.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪