♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 25=
Thinking about shootings lately,
I think I'm quite in a good state.
Su Xiao.
I think you're at your best
during our cooperation this time.
Thank you, director.
Though we've just cooperated twice.
I will perform better in the future.
It's so great that
you've played this role.
But what's embarrassing is,
maybe some audience will hate you again.
After all, it's a hateful role.
Then it proves that I acted well.
Actually you're very cute in the reality.
The audience have been cheated by you.
Yeah.
It's actually not bad
to play a female villain.
It seems that I enjoy playing even more.
You just want to be famous?
Or you want to be an excellent actress?
Think it over.
=Unidentified Number=
Who's this?
Hi.
Sorry to call you so suddenly.
This is Li Xiwei.
Mr. Li?
I got your phone number from someone else.
Anything that needs my help?
Can I dine out with you on this weekend?
I'm really sorry.
You'll be working that day?
Reporters of the tabloids
will cook up news based on a few photos.
So even your family
will be involved into trouble.
We're unfamiliar and
there's no reason for a treat.
Well, I borrowed you a handkerchief
on the reception, right?
Could you give it back to me?
Take this.
I'll mail it to you after washing it.
That handkerchief is very valuable.
I wish that you could
give it to me face-to-face.
See you on the weekend.
Welcome to Scorpio Club.
May I ask, are you Ms. Su Xiao?
Yes.
Let me keep your coat.
Thanks.
Excuse me, Su Xiao.
I made you come here dining with me.
It's good that you know it.
This restaurant is
limited to membership guests.
Paparazzi won't come to take photos.
Just be relaxed.
I see.
So you're pretty thoughtful.
I have some connections in the media.
I heard that you bumped into
some troubles before.
But don't worry, I've given them a lesson.
They won't be impertinent again.
Okay. Thanks for such a
valuable handkerchief.
It must be very expensive.
The price doesn't matter.
The reason why it's valuable
is that it carries a memory of you and me.
So scaring.
Don't be afraid. Don't.
I'm just kidding.
A mind reader?
That's more scaring then.
If my attitude was too tough,
allow me to apologize to you officially.
Please don't be mad at me, okay?
No, I'm not mad.
My face just doesn't look friendly.
If there's nothing else, I'd better...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is a nutritious set meal
for women to keep fit.
Please try it.
I invited you over here
to talk about the exclusive contract.
But I already refused it before.
But I said that
I would keep trying, didn't I?
To be honest,
I've prepared three good scripts
with you playing the heroines.
And the hottest themes.
=Xiao Jian Calling=
Damn it.
I'd better hang it up first.
Just pick it up.
Hi.
Where have you gone?
Didn't I tell you to inform Sandy first
if there's anything urgent?
I'm dining with someone.
You just got photographed
by the paparazzi!
You've forgotten it so soon?
I won't be photographed here!
I'll be back soon.
Where are you?
I'll tell Sandy to drive you back.
No need, I'll be back very soon.
Welcome to Scorpio Club.
He heard it...
Hey, you really don't need to come here...
He hangs it up...
What do you say?
If you sign with me, I think your career
will arrive at a higher level very soon.
Maybe.
Su Xiao.
I'm really very sincere.
I want to make you popular.
Oh...
What's up?
You seem absent-minded.
Sorry. Sorry.
Is it because of the call just now?
Your boyfriend?
No. No. I don't have a boyfriend.
Well, I'd better go back first.
Let's go Dutch.
I see.
Got it.
Mr. Xiao Jian, please wait a minute.
I'm really sorry.
This gentleman insisted...
Never mind.
Back to your work.
Hi, isn't this Xiao Jian?
What brought you here?
Long time no see, Li Xiwei.
My assistant hadn't come
back home so late at night.
I was afraid that she
might run into some bad guy.
So I came pick her up.
If you mean Su Xiao, just rest easy.
I'm here. No bad guy
dare get close to her.
That's hard to say.
Some guy looks like a gentleman.
But he's thinking about
some hideous plan deep down.
It's safe only when I'm with her.
I think I've seen this scene just now!
So, do you mind joining us?
No, thanks.
Why didn't you tell me about this first?
Sorry.
I made Su Xiao come here to see me.
I hope that you won't do this again.
Now, let's go back.
Sorry.
But you don't have the right to
interfere with her personal life, right?
Because she's mine.
His? I'm his?
But she told me that
she doesn't have a boyfriend.
I mean, she's signed with me.
So I should take care of her.
You should have said it clear!
I see.
You said that she's your assistant.
So I thought she hasn't signed
any broker company.
Actually, she's going to negotiate
for a very important project.
So can we leave now?
It seems that
it's because I'm ill-informed.
Why I heard that she just has to
play some petty villains lately?
We're considering for artists
in a long run.
Unlike some company, they just pursue
short-term popularity by dirty means
and dump the artists
after drying out their value.
Is that so?
But does your company know it's traffic
that matters the most in this era.
If no views,
even if you're the movie king,
you'll be forgotten by the audience.
What should I do? What should I do?
What should I do!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪