♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 31=
Damn it.
Su Xiao! Get up! Su Xiao!
What's up? What happened?
It's a storm! Too dangerous here!
We have to go up!
Are you kidding?
Hurry, get up!
Sorry.
Maybe because I was too tired,
I slept like a log.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have
put up tents on the beach.
But you did that to...
Don't know how severe the storm would be.
Let's go hide in the cave
that we saw in the daytime.
Okay.
This...
The boards have been blown away.
What should we do?
Watch out!
Come!
But I...
Hurry, hold my hand!
I...
Su Xiao!
Don't be afraid. Trust me.
Let's go.
Okay.
This is not arranged by them, right?
You think they
got the Rain God to do this?
Sandy must be so worried about us.
I don't think
they could come here before it's fine.
At present, we have to rely on ourselves.
Are you okay?
What's up?
Nothing...
Well...
Your clothes...
My clothes?
I go check outside.
You just stay here.
Oh.
Are you alright?
Where have you been?
I tore off all the cameras.
Ah, why did you...
You want to be filmed like this?
Don't worry.
I've left a message before the cameras.
Can they see it?
Even if they can't,
they'll come here to investigate.
Anyway, we should find a way to warm up.
You're right.
Luckily, I've brought a lighter.
Now the problem is
to find something to burn.
I'll go pick up
some twigs from outside, wait for me.
No, you can't go out.
It's okay.
If anything bad happens,
you can rescue me.
It'll be too late by then.
Leave it to me.
Then try to find those dry twigs.
Okay.
Sorry, it took a long time.
Although I picked up so much,
it's all wet.
Probably can't be lit.
It's okay. Thank you.
Look.
Although the surface iswet,
they're dry inside.
You also learned this from your father?
Um, yes.
Great!
Now we can survive the night.
We're finally warm.
Seems that you can
have another image, Bear Grylls.
Actually, camping with my dad
didn't always give me happy memories.
You don't like camping?
I was quite happy at first.
I looked ferocious.
Other kids often got scared.
So I couldn't make any friends.
Then I became reluctant to play outside.
On festivals or holidays,
other kids all played outside home.
Only I stayed in my room in a daze.
But one day,
I overheard that
the reason why dad took me to camp
was that he thought it's pitiful to see me
staying alone...
I didn't like to show
my true feelings back then.
So I had a fight with him.
Since then, I stopped go camping.
Didn't expect what I learned back then
could be so useful today.
Your father actually
treated you very well.
Um.
You've been caring about
your look since then?
Um.
But actually I just felt like
that it's my own problem.
I didn't want to
rely on my family to solve it.
I wanted to find
a road that belongs to myself.
A road that I could walk down
till its end regardless of this look.
So you became an actress?
Um.
But I can never
say sorry to my father any more.
You can't?
Your father must be
protecting you from far away.
Um.
Let's go visit his grave after going back.
His... His grave?
Your father's.
When did my father get a grave?
He didn't...
Of course, he's still alive.
He's... Alive?
He's well alive.
He watches my TV shows
every day back in my hometown.
He's so happy.
But you just said you can't apologize?
Missed the best timing.
How embarrassing if I apologize now!
Well, don't pretend to be strong.
What, you want my dad to be dead?
No. But you... Your emotion just now...
I said he's alive.
Why are you so annoying?
We're not in some romance drama now.
We're in the reality, reality, you know?
Did your IQ get lowered by those plays?
How can we encounter those absurd plots?
You silly cat.
You didn't say it clearly!
What are you doing, freak!
Silly cat. Stupid cat!
Freak! You big freak!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪