♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 23=
You're still stubborn.
Oh, I saw the online drama you starred.
Thank you, sis Yan. Thanks.
Li Yan, let's talk about other things.
The role doesn't seem right for you.
Excuse me, your dishes.
Thank you.
Don't get it wrong.
I'm not saying you didn't play it well.
Oppositely, as an actress
who has never challenged such a role,
you've done a great job.
Even so, the roles you've played have left
great impression on audience.
They would be naturally
influenced by that impression.
I've met the same problem.
Su Xiao, you've a
characteristic appearance.
That's more impressive.
However, that's not a bad thing for you.
Although your appearance doesn't quite
match the current style
of the leading roles,
I like it very much.
Especially your eyes.
But my eyes look fierce.
They always say I can only play villains.
You got determined eyes.
It's easy to touch people.
As an actress, it's an admirable talent.
So, you don't need to worry about this.
What you've to do then
is to try different roles.
To accumulate experience bit by bit.
Experience?
Even you got all the villain roles.
But each work wants
different things from the role.
Do keep it in mind.
The work does not exist to
improve the image of the actor.
While the meaning of an actor is
to improve the quality of the work.
Alright, that's all
I wanna say about work.
Let's enjoy the food now.
Li Yan cares about you.
I think she specially
came to enlighten you.
What's up?
I'm eating now.
No matter how much people praise her...
It tastes so good!
It still can't compare with
her idol's few words.
Yes, tastes good.
Here you are. We brought some for you.
Food in this restaurant is really nice.
Li Yan recommended it to us.
I'm going on location as of tomorrow.
No need to prepare meals for me.
Yes. Xiaoxiao is alone
at home then. Right?
Then I think you can get off me.
Well... Fingers crossed.
I got things to do.
Why you two are acting
like middle school students?
Ready!
=Rating: 6.3=
Xiaoxiao!
Director Gao called me.
Ah?
He said he wanted you to
play a role in his drama.
Thank you for coming in person.
Director Gao, you're welcome.
It's me who should say thanks.
Xiao Jian is not with you?
He has spare time,
but I don't want him to come.
What about your bet?
It's been settled.
He said I can make decisions on my own.
That's great.
It means he has totally trusted you.
Er... A little, maybe.
You did very well in my film last time.
But I think I haven't made
your acting fully shown.
So...
I've thought it over and over again.
I can't just let it go at that.
So, I'd like to cooperate with you again!
Maybe it sounds kinda emotional,
but I've already taken you as my partner.
This time,
the role I want you to play is...
It's a villain. Quite vicious villain.
It's okay. Don't hurry to reply me.
Okay.
I'd like to do it. A villain.
=Su Xiao Calling=
Hello.
Are you available now?
I'm just taking a break,
but not much time.
I agreed with
Director Gao to play the role.
The budget is not high,
so not a long shooting period.
I see.
The most vicious villain by far.
I will definitely do it well.
Okay. Since you're playing it,
do it the best.
=So far!=
=We're playing ball, be gentle to me=
We're in a traffic jam now.
It may last long as I see.
I really wanna go home early
and rest in my bed.
What's that cat doing now?
She should be
studying the script like crazy.
What's wrong? Are you alright?
Who is that man!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪