♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean♪♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 29=
Alright, finally it's the last section
of today's Sprint Partners.
Looking for Coconuts!
This game requires all the players
to enter the coast snack street
to find coconuts with your team mark
on it from the stalls.
Every team has five coconuts to find out.
The team that collects all the coconuts
and comes back the fastest wins.
But the stall owners might not
hand out the coconuts at once.
So players must complete
the tasks they assigned
as soon as possible to get the coconuts.
What's more,
the winner will get 100 scores!
So even the team that lags behind
could take this chance
to make a turnaround!
Go for it, everyone.
So the previous scores would be useless...
That's why we call it a variety show.
So, game starts now!
Three, two, one!
We're going to find star marks.
Let's start from nearby.
Okay, there's a stall ahead.
Let's go take a look.
Here you are.
Looks so delicious.
Hi, do you have any coconut
with a star mark on it?
Good luck for you.
I suppose it's here?
Yes, it is.
Can you give it to us?
Yes, I can.
But there's a condition.
Aren't you actors? Give me a play first.
A piece of cake.
What play is it?
You'll play a cat fairy.
And you'll play a Taoist to catch her.
Well, could it be something else?
No.
I just want to see
Taoist catching cat fairy.
Just to play a cat, okay?
I can play anything else
for you but not this!
Give me the coconut now!
Sorry, your coconut, please spare my life.
Su Xiao is so interesting.
Didn't expect
it's so helpful to be scary-looking.
Next, leave it to me.
I'm expecting you
have better means to get coconuts.
Do you have any coconut
with a star mark on it?
Yes, here it is.
Thank you.
But the program
asked me not to tell you that
the fruit stall next door,
the dessert shop ahead
and the stuffed bun shop
all have your coconuts.
Thank you very much.
And please take this and eat it.
Well, you finished the task so fast.
The fans are so enthusiastic.
Neither of other two teams
has found three coconuts yet.
Indeed.
It's also troublesome to be so popular.
Where did you get so many donuts?
The stall owner over there gave it to us.
She told us to eat it.
Will this affect this program's effects?
Maybe, more or less.
Makes sense.
You two.
Um?
You still haven't finished the task.
What?
Just now,
when the stall owner gave you the coconut,
she told you to eat the donuts, right?
So eating up the donuts is
the premise for you to get the coconuts.
But you haven't. So your task is still on.
So yummy.
Mine too.
Each one has a unique flavor.
Really? Let me try yours.
Aren't you too greedy?
Eat yours up first.
This tastes good, too.
You greedy kitten!
Yummy. Yours tastes good, too.
But it seems as natural as it was.
What's going on between them?
The vibe seems good.
This tastes good, too.
Yes. I can eat so much more.
Help, I'm so full now.
Me too.
I can't eat any more.
Only two left, come on.
Now, let's see the final rankings.
The last place of the Sprint Partners is
the Blue team of Xiao Jian and Su Xiao!
I'm gonna throw up.
Me too.
The punishment for them is,
a two-day survival test
on a desert island starting from tomorrow.
As the last section of our program,
you two are gonna withstand
a two-day survival test
on a desert island.
Filming equipment has been set up there.
We'll watch your moves
on another island nearby.
Could there be any problems?
Don't worry,
everything has been arranged well.
There's no dangerous animals
on the island.
The food supply is sufficient.
And they'll take all the necessary tools.
And we've set many secret cameras
to monitor them from 360-degree.
Don't worry.
That's exactly what I'm worried about.
It's okay, Sandy.
We're expecting
you two's brilliant performance.
Okay, we'll try our best.
Anything wrong?
Nothing.
So, target at the desert land, set out!
No one is here, as they said.
Where the cameras could be?
What the hell.
Watch your tongue.
A drone just flew by.
And we both have sound recorders on us.
Anyway, let's start probing this island.
Okay, good luck.
Here's a cave.
Be careful.
There might be cameras here.
Anyway, we can't be more careful.
After a tour,
I think this island is not big.
What should we do next?
It's almost dark.
I think it's time to
get prepared for the night.
Prepare for the night?
Su Xiao, could you come up here
and give me a hand?
Okay.
Well...
Although it's a program being filmed,
I still feel panic
if he and I have to stay here
together for two days and a night.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back♪♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪