♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 04=
Studying performance?
Now I know he was lying!
He has never planned to
get serious jobs for me, right?
No!
I'm so angry! So angry!
I got to protest! Protest!
Protest!
Listen.
You talked about the contract every day.
But there's only me who's been
performing the contract.
You...
So close. So close.
The nation is cheated by his look like this, right?
Were you
peeping at me?
What are you talking about?
What's to peep at?
You think you're handsome?
What a dishonest kitten.
If you dare talk to me like this again,
I'll burn all those clothes down!
Honey.
You two really get along well with each other.
Sa... Sandy.
Hi, Su Xiao.
Remember to call me Sis Sandy.
Sis Sandy.
What brought you here?
About the audition...
Did you get the script?
They've sent it to us.
You said that you need to check it.
So,
look,
I came here right away.
Come on in first.
Wait.
I was going to say that
I've been here for so long,
but where's the job that you promised?
Oh, right.
I've handled the job.
In a few days,
you'll have an audition.
Jianjian, you didn't tell her that?
I tried hard to get it.
A role in director Xu's new movie.
Yes, the super famous
big director who often
shoots action movies.
Director Xu.
Director Xu!
Director Xu...
Congrats! You'll be
on the big screen!
Thank you.
Everyone!
So great!
Alright.
Meal time.
So many dishes.
What's wrong?
Did you
call food delivery instead?
You made so many dishes in such a short time.
And it tastes good.
Isn't it really not food delivery?
Will you die if you just praise me?!
Okay.
You better stop being an actress.
Go work as a cook.
Then I might turn you into a cha siu baau.
Looks so yummy.
Sis Sandy.
Xiaoxiao is so awesome.
I know Sis Sandy is the best to me.
Is it done?
Of course.
Okay.
Let's go to the study.
Wait.
I made a big effort to cook this.
Don't you waste food.
Eat it up first.
Fine.
Let's eat first.
Such delicious food.
Can I eat it with you?
Of course.
After all, I cook so well.
=Frost Cold As Blood
Movie Script\Confidential=
Come, here you are.
What's this?
Director Xu's movie it is.
This is the script.
Listen to me,
the roles are all set.
Hurry, check it out.
Such big news, why didn't you tell me earlier?
Eat what?
A waste of time!
Unbelievable.
What an annoying woman.
Here it is.
It's finally coming.
I've been enduring everything
just for this kind of a day.
Goodbye.
Villain specialist.
Hello.
A brand-new self.
Go for it, honey.
Are you kidding me?!
A cold-blooded
female killer disguised as a man.
A villain.
Why this kind of role again?
Yes.
Isn't it the role most suitable for you?
You liar, rascal, scoundrel!
Cheater, shameless, despicable, pervert!
You... You...
You...
Freak!
Do I need to get her back?
Nuts.
You're so ruthless.
What damn contract.
And resources?
And connections?
Nothing
changed.
Liar! Freak! Liar!
Liar!
Freak!
=Director Gao calling=
What's the matter?
Su.
It's me.
Gao Dashang.
What do you want?
You want me to beat you again, huh?
=Director Gao communicating=
You...
So bad-tempered.
No.
Actually, my new movie starts
looking for casting.
It's just an idol drama with little investment.
I need a kind and cute heroine.
What do you say.
I wonder
if you're still interested.
I'm in.
I'll play the role.
I'm glad that you can play it.
But why Xiao Jian
and Sandy think...
Can't be more vulgar!
But you just open the script.
The first three pages tell everything.
I don't agree with you to play this role.
Although the script is dull,
I want to play it!
Kind and cute heroine.
It's my dream!
You both said my script is dull...
What do you know?
An actress chooses a role
based on if she can harness it,
not she likes it or not.
A super star like you
who can always get what you want
can never understand a neglected grass-root
like me who crave for a good role.
I didn't mean that.
Mr. Gao, keep away from them
in case we would be hurt as well.
Well, well.
I knew you've been looking down upon me!
But I'll play the role well to prove you wrong!
Fine.
Since you're so brave,
take this role then.
But you must take the role
that I chose for you as well.
Let's make a bet
on these two roles.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪