♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 17=
Su Xiao,
how have you been doing these days?
Have you got any troubles?
I'm all fine these days.
Who the hell started the rumor last time?
Did you find that?
If you stir up trouble again,
I'll post the audio file online.
It doesn't matter who did that.
I promised you I would
cook you a rich meal, that matters.
I'm starving.
Wow! It's just like the
level of a five-star chef!
I'm just fond of cooking.
When I eat something delicious outside,
I'd try to cook it at home.
I gotta take a photo and share in Moments.
What a pity! Sandy didn't come today.
Speaking of this,
we haven't seen him for days.
That's it.
He told me he's looking into something.
Don't know what's going on.
I heard that he was going to
see Xiao Jian.
What the hell are they doing so covertly?
I mean they're planning something good.
Well, guys! Cheers!
Cheers!
Enjoy yourselves!
It's so tasty!
Ms. Su Xiao!
What fabulous cooking skills you have!
-So palatable! -Yep! So delicious!
Well, it seems they recognize
my cooking skills more than my acting.
Nice! I finally repaid sis Yan the favor.
Sandy?
Su Xiao,
I've something important to tell you.
Okay, it's done.
Thank you.
You're gonna finish your scenes today.
I'll miss you.
Ms. Su.
May I be your personal assistant?
I really, really admire
your acting skills!
I wanna be with you in the future!
Thank you for your kindness.
But, sorry, I can't accept that.
I would never keep one around me
who is always ready to betray me.
Su Xiao,
I've something important to tell you.
These days,
I've asked someone to look into
the source of those candid photos online.
Didn't Liu Xuxu do that?
Yes. She did spread the photos.
But those photos
were taken by someone else.
It's your makeup assistant, Yao Mengfang.
Yao Mengfang, have I ever offended you?
You must take it wrong!
How could I...
Take it wrong?
You mean I've wronged you?
Liu Xuxu.
She asked you to do this, right?
She said I would get a large sum of money
if I just took some photos.
I don't have a regular work.
And I've to pay for all the makeup tools.
Sometimes, I can hardly
find a crew to follow.
Thus, I even can't afford my rent.
At first, I refused her.
Later, she told me this
can also hype the film up.
It might also do you some good!
And you would accept this.
Not me. It does you some good.
I'm sorry, I know I did wrong.
You think I'm going to
let you off the hook
by making such a casual apology?
Forget it!
What?
You must be kidding, right?
Do you think I'm just kidding?
It's settled.
No more preferential treatment for Liu Xuxu.
Would it work?
She has a big investor backing her up.
So what? I'm Li Xiwei,
I can choose whoever I want.
Who dares to say no?
Besides, that may not
be a bad thing for her.
Well, Mr. Li, may I ask...
Do you pay your attention to someone else?
What kind of person is that?
Good question.
That's what I wanna know.
You think I'm going to
let you off the hook
by making such a casual apology?
If I make the things
you've done known to everyone,
can you find a place
to stay in this industry?
Will you get another job?
It's terrible, isn't it?
You did get the benefit for now,
but you may also ruin your career.
I can keep it a secret this time.
But, Yao Mengfang,
I hope you can get a lesson from it.
You can easily
find a chance in the showbiz
to gain something
by harming others' interests.
If you only think a lot of
the petty benefits at the moment,
you may lose the thing
that can never be retrieved.
Don't even think about
being my personal assistant.
If you do such a thing again,
I'll let everyone know what you've done.
I'm terribly sorry.
I won't do that anymore.
Behave yourself.
Xiaoxiao. You still chose to spare her.
Or else? After all,
she's not the prime plotter.
You may meet a lot of
"Liu Xuxu" in the future.
I'm not afraid at all.
Just bring it on!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don’t you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪