♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 14=
So tired. I got pain all over.
Xiaoxiao, may I come in?
Come on in!
You had a long day today.
It's alright.
You got torture scenes tomorrow, you okay?
Don't worry.
Although you won't get trauma
with a layer of artificial skin,
it still hurts to be whipped.
Never mind.
I can bear this since it's all for our movie.
It's okay. Sis Sandy, don't worry about me.
Xiaoxiao.
=Frost Cold As Blood
The Seventh Day of Shooting=
Can Su Xiao bear this?
Shall we let the stand-in do this?
It's close shot this time.
She asked to do it herself so as not to bloop.
Try to finish it at the first try.
All divisions, get ready.
Okay.
Su Xiao, I'll try to control my strength.
Never mind. Just make the scene perfect.
Otherwise, there's no point in my doing so.
Okay.
Alright. Ready to start.
Guys! Camera on! Get ready.
It's okay. I can do it.
Ready. Action!
How dare you betray me!
It hurts so much.
I brought you up. That's how you repay me?
Father, I know I'm wrong.
Good. One last line.
Next time, I do take her...
Cut! Who is that!
I'm sorry, it's kinda chilly. I...
Don't you know it's synchronously recording?
Get out of here!
I'm terribly sorry.
Liu Xuxu!
I gotta scratch your plastic face!
Sandy! Calm down! Calm down!
Shut up! You guys with no duty, just get out!
Let me go! Let me go!
Su Xiao, can you hold on?
If you can't, the stand-in can do this.
I'm okay, director. One more time.
Su Xiao.
I wanna make it perfect, please.
Okay, one more! Make it the best!
Got it!
Cut! Perfect!
Are you alright, Su Xiao?
I'm fine, how is it, director?
Better than the last one.
Well done.
Oh, my poor girl.
Just praise me, okay?
Do you remember what I said last night?
Never mind.
I can bear this since it's all for our movie.
Xiaoxiao.
But listen to me, don't push yourself so hard.
Rest assured. I think
I finally got the chance I've been waiting.
I wanna exert all my efforts.
It doesn't matter even if I get hurts.
Otherwise, I will regret it in the future.
Good girl.
Well done, Xiaoxiao.
Thank you, Sis Sandy.
It's done.
You've to go back for something, right?
You're hurt now, I'd better be with you.
Never mind, I'm fine.
Well, I'll go and come back tomorrow night.
Bring me some delicious food.
Okay.
Coming.
How is Su Xiao?
We come to see her.
Is Ms. Su alright?
She's fine, don't worry.
Su Xiao.
Okay, that's all for today's shooting. Thank you.
Well done. Go back early and have a good rest.
Okay, thanks, director.
Why is this place so spooky at night?
I should have gone with them.
Why I feel that someone is following me.
What to do? It's a long way from the hotel.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪