♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 15=
Stay calm. In this case,
I should...
Don't move!
It's me.
Why you?
I scared you?
I was scared to death!
Mad?
How dare you laugh!
If you were a second later,
I would have crushed your foot!
And kicked you off, okay!
What brought you here?
What? Of course it's because I felt lonely.
I felt so lonely since I couldn't
touch “my cat” every day!
Hands off me! Don't you touch my hair!
I heard that you did the flogging scene in person?
Yes. The director also praised me
that I did so well.
Are you made of iron?
With a layer of artificial skin,
you dared to get whipped?
You have a thick skin?
Do you think the props are made for fun?
What if you get hurt?
What if the shooting is delayed? That matters.
Just hurts a little. Won't get trauma.
It would be too late if you get trauma.
So you're here to scold me?
Not that.
I come to play with “my cat”!
Thanks for sending me back.
Save it till you back home.
Get lost!
You idiot! Freak! Idiotic freak!
Hello, Sandy.
The news is done.
It'll be released tomorrow morning.
Well done.
I'm going back to the hotel.
Did you contact Su Xiao?
Yes.
Was she happy to hear your voice?
Maybe.
What's this?
=Su Xiao did flogging scene in person=
What's going on?
Was there a reporter on the scene?
=Comments: Sis, don't get hurt!=
=She is so professional!=
I didn't find that!
They're praising me! OMG!
Tell that freak now.
I have to impress him this time!
=Xiao Jian=
Video call?
He saw the news?
Why that fast?
Could it be...
I saw the news.
You did so well.
Gosh! What to do? Help me!
Who can help me? I'll feel shy and blush!
No way! I can't let him find that.
=Su Xiao=
She is not up yet?
What kept me waiting so long?
You know,
a fairy like me needs time to come down to earth.
Come down to earth? With face down?
What's up?
I'm going to Egypt today.
It's boring to fly for ten hours.
Does it have to do with me?
Why called me so early in the morning!
I also have something to tell you.
Well. In this case, I'll be generous and forgive you.
Do listen carefully to what I'm about to tell you.
And keep it in mind.
In fact...
I love you so much!
Stay with me, okay?
You... You... What're you doing?
No, no, no! Not me! It's Liu Xuxu next door.
Liu Xuxu! Not me!
Sorry, I gotta hang up.
Wait! Wait for a second!
What?
Record it now! Hurry!
Why record this? I gotta hang up.
Listen. This hotel was booked for the whole crew,
no outsider can live in.
Don't you wanna know who Liu Xuxu is talking to?
How is it going?
That's indeed Liu Xuxu.
Who is that man?
I heard Liu Xuxu called him Mr. Lin in the middle.
So? Who is that?
There is only one who surnamed Lin in the crew,
don't you know?
I see.
Lin Hao is one of the investors of this movie.
This gossip really diverts me.
Hope you won't tease me to divert yourself.
Let me get you a new cat outfit to
show my apology, okay?
Is that an apology?
Idiot. Anyway, it's really an interesting gossip.
I forgot to tell him the news that I got praised.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪