♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 20=
Su Xiao! Thank god!
I thought you got lost!
Sandy! Where have you gone?
Hey, you! Did you bully Su Xiao?
No! No! Not like that.
Not like that, I'm just too nervous
and restless because I couldn't find you.
Really? Nothing happened?
I wonder if I have the honor to
invite you to sign with our company?
I'm relived then.
Well, I gotta go now.
=CEO Li Xiwei=
Su Xiao, I'm very sincere.
Can I think it carefully?
Surely, you can. If you're interested,
this is my name card,
you can contact me at any time.
Oh, no!
Hey! As my assistant,
how dare you not answer my calls!
Fine. You didn't answer my calls?
I gotta add it into the contract
that you've to answer
my call as soon as I call!
Forget it. I forgive you this time.
What the hell did he wanna say?
I nearly forgot the business.
You're done with the film, right?
Well... You're working very hard.
Em... Have a good sleep. Good night.
Good night.
=Su Xiao and Li Xiwei are so intimate!=
When did we get shot?
=Xiao Jian, Video Call=
A bad feeling rises.
Hello?
Hey! That photo! Explain to me!
That... I... I...
Don't stutter!
What if the media made up a story?
How to solve that then!
That's his company's party.
Sandy was also with me!
What's so strange about that?
Why you're so mad?
Well... You can't dance well.
And you got shot and posted online.
That will affect your job in the future!
Huh? I danced well, okay!
Really?
I can show you now if you don't buy that!
Go ahead then.
Mr. Xiao, may I invite you
to dance with me?
Sure. Please.
Ready, go! One, two, three, four.
Not so good.
What?
Back straight.
It's pretty straight, okay!
Straighter than a mongoose!
Your center of balance.
Be careful. Don't step on my feet.
So annoying.
Keep up with the pace.
But... How to say.
I feel so relaxed.
Well... Danced well.
I... I've to get up early tomorrow.
Oh, yes.
Good night.
Never thought we really
came to a terrific place.
Would you hate me if we died?
I'm hating you now.
Cut! Wonderful!
You mean she danced with Li Xiwei?
Su Xiao told me that.
I'm worried the media will hype it up.
That will do her bad.
Do you want me to do something?
No need. If we take the released news off,
that will draw people's attention.
As long as another
bigger news is released,
no one will pay attention to her news.
Hey, Xiao.
Ready for the next scene.
I gotta hang up.
Checking your phone again?
You've been checking
your phone a lot lately.
You're in a relationship?
Not that.
My six-year-old daughter told me
she would be your wife in the future.
Don't have an affair.
What are you talking about?
Hurry up. They're urging us.
Wait.
Let's take a photo, okay?
What's up? Why so mushy?
Serving the fans is also part of my job.
I'll tell your broker about this.
If so, you've to take one for my daughter.
Unbelievable, my kitten,
see what I've done for you.
=Top Chinese and American stars
appear together!=
=Xiao Jian's telling
things about filming at Hollywood=
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪