♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 21=
=Top Chinese and American stars
appear together!=
=Xiao Jian's telling
things about filming at Hollywood=
It's trending No.1 just a blink of an eye.
No one now cares about me
dancing with Li Xiwei.
Did he do this on purpose? To help me.
What if the media made up a story?
How to solve that then!
If I signed with Li Xiwei,
it might become a hard nut to crack.
=Mr. Li, sorry, I have to turn down
your offer of the exclusive contract=
Okay.
I've refused him.
Hey!
=Xiao Jian=
Scared me!
Gosh! His message.
Director Gao's drama is gonna be released.
I'm looking forward to
the outcome of our bet.
A bet?
On what?
Which role that you play is more popular
after the two works get released?
If the role that you choose wins,
no matter what kind of role
you want to play,
I'll help you get it.
It's all up to you.
However,
if the role that I choose wins,
in the future,
you can only play the roles
that I choose for you.
It'll be out soon.
=Su Da: Xiaoxiao=
Brother?
Xiaoxiao, we haven't been in touch lately.
Have you been eating regularly?
I'm waiting for you to see the drama
in which you first starred as the heroine.
I'm your biggest fan.
My brother is so cute.
=The day the Taste Of Summer is released=
I'm back!
And me!
=The awkward vibe=
I... Can't I watch it alone in my room?
Come on! We're all here to accompany you.
That's right. Xiaoxiao.
It's the premiere day of
your first heroine drama!
Since when did you two hit it off so well?
I'm so shame-making!
Alright. It's coming soon.
Kind of excited.
Xiaowei! Xiaowei.
You...
Xiaowei. Really you.
Sorry, I'm not leaving you alone again.
If you dare do
such a dangerous thing again,
I'll never forgive you.
=The Taste of Summer=
Xiaoxiao, that's good.
I can feel the inner world of this role.
Really? Thank you.
You know, Su Xiao starred it.
I just thought
she would definitely kill the man!
Nice role. But not Su Xiao's style.
I still prefer the style
she showed before.
Am I right? Speaking of Su Xiao,
everyone's going to
think it's a vicious...
What's wrong? Did I say anything wrong?
Never mind. You don't need to comfort me.
After all, it's the first time
I starred this kind role.
It's hard to change the impression.
=The Taste of Summer. Rating: 6.3=
I dare not see this! Dear me!
I've never been so nervous!
Nice role. But not Su Xiao's style.
I still prefer the style
she showed before.
Well then, I'm lost?
No! I can't get disheartened!
No matter what setback I'm facing,
I cannot be upset.
Keep going when I'm full!
=Sandy Calling=
Hello?
Xiaoxiao, are you alright?
I'm fine. What's up?
It's not easy to try a brand new style.
But you have me with you all the time.
Thank you, Sandy.
You're welcome.
Well. Xiao Jian contacted me.
He said he has finished
the shooting at Hollywood.
Then he'll come back to do the rest.
He'll be home tomorrow night.
I see.
I'll come to see you two tomorrow.
So I told you in advance.
Okay.
Alright, I've been full up.
Cheer up!
Xiao Jian is coming back.
We haven't seen for days.
Although we've had video calls,
about the bet, don't know what he will...
Long time no see, Su Xiao,
how have you been doing?
Forget about the bet.
Just smile.
'Cause I like seeing your smile the most.
No! No! No! How could he be like this.
Maybe he would just be like this...
Long time no see! My cat!
Come on! Come on! Smile.
Freak. A freak comes from Hollywood.
Okay! Here comes the final part
of the Sprint Partners!
This show is so popular lately.
The guests are all big stars.
Go for it!
Hope you can show perfect cooperation.
You're back...
Your fans are watching you.
Alright! Coconut searching game!
You... What happened?
Begins now!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪