♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 01=
Where are you rushing to?
You think you can escape from me?
Stop dreaming.
Cut.
Okay. Let's check it out.
Can you let go of me now?
Sorry.
I didn't mean to.
From where did they get such a horrible aunt?
Unbelievable.
Xin, you acted so well.
I even became worried.
Really?
You bet.
Come.
Clean it up.
Your hair is wet.
Don't get a cold.
Okay.
What does that little girl know?!
“Horrible aunt”?
That's called acting skill!
Playing villains also entails acting skills!
I've played 42 bad female supporting
roles since graduation!
Doesn't that show my experience and seniority?!
I don't want bad roles, either.
I also want to play the heroine!
You think I want to play the bad guy?
No more bad guys. No more.
I'm quitting even if I'll lose my job!
At worst I'll stop being an actress!
I'll find another job! I'll be a worker!
No more bad roles.
No.
I still want to be an actress.
I'm not gonna give up on it.
I'll be the heroine next time.
I won't quit!
=Director Gao=
Director Gao.
Hello, is that director Gao?
Yes.
Su.
Director Gao.
What can I do for you?
Here is the thing.
I'm considering
an audition for the heroine in my next work.
The heroine?
If you're interested,
come to my room right now.
Very interested!
On my way now!
I'll be there right now!
Damn it.
I wouldn't have drunk so much if I knew this.
I didn't expect that...
Director would call me at this moment.
But so late at night...
No, I want to throw up.
But it seems that...
All right, I better not think too much.
Finally, someone wants me to play
the heroine...
Yes.
Hurry come here.
Sorry.
I called you here so late at night.
It's okay.
I really
appreciate it that you could give me
such a good
opportunity.
What's wrong?
Why this kind of expression?
Nothing.
I'm just too happy.
=Sorry to make you watch this unpleasant scene=
Oops.
That vomit ruins my opportunity.
I'm really sorry.
You're fine now?
Yes, I'm fine.
But I stained your clothes.
Never mind.
As long as you can compensate me.
Compensate?
Yes.
Compensate!
What are you doing?
I know that.
You've been longing to get rid of bad roles, right?
But based on your conditions,
I think there's no director
willing to make you a heroine, right?
What?
What's wrong with my conditions?
As long as you obey me,
you'll enjoy endless wealth and honor,
and you'll always be the heroine.
Aren't these lines too old-fashioned?
How can you be a director by that?
Impudence!
You're just a third-rate actress.
How dare you talk back to a director?
Look into the mirror,
don't you know you have a face of villain?
It's lucky for you to be liked by me.
How dare you not accept it
but satirize me?!
If you don't listen to me,
you'll specialize in playing
spicy villains for a lifetime!
You'll never be the heroine!
Action
You gotta
shut up!
Taking advantage of me?
Are you kidding me?
I can accept it if you say my acting is bad.
But how should you say
I can never play the heroine?
Wait. Wait.
Wait.
Wait!
Look at these super stars.
Believe me.
Although I'm still a petty director now,
I'll be very capable in the future.
As long as I try best to make you popular...
You failed to take advantage of me.
So you started cursing me?
No.
I didn't mean that.
Having this face,
is it my fault?!
Ever since I went to elementary school,
due to this hellish look,
I got edged out of the games of my classmates.
When I was in high school,
I met a kid who got lost.
I meant to comfort him.
But his parents took me as a human trader.
After I became an actress,
I had my first role as a malicious female villain.
I played it so successfully.
So I become a villain specialist.
You want me to beat you?
I understand.
Once I was also a director caring about the world.
After graduation,
I've been dreaming of make a good work.
But no one invested in me.
I had no choice but to start from third-rate ads.
I worked harder and harder.
After having struggled for so many years,
It's my first time to do this actually.
Didn't expect that even a third-rate star
would ignore me.
=Third-rate Actress=
You could have saved the last sentence.
However,
I think I can understand you.
Although it's hard for us now,
if we continue working hard
for the sake of our dream,
one day,
we both will realize our dream.
Director Gao!
Su Xiao!
Casting couch, director Gao?
Sorry to interrupt you.
Xiao Jian...
Xiao Jian.
The famous movie king.
Works starred by him got awarded
several times at various movie festivals.
Meanwhile he's also a board member of
a film and television tycoon in China.
He's invested many brilliant films
and television works.
He's a household name.
And he has a positive image.
Very popular.
He's called the No.1 caring boy
in the showbiz.
So, right now,
what's
going on here?
Boss Xiao.
The fact is not what you've seen.
It's a misunderstanding.
It's a sheer misunderstanding.
I hate it most that directors
misuse authority in the cast.
I bet you know that?
Su.
Hurry, please help me explain it.
We were just having a heart-to-heart talk, right?
But you talked about endless
wealth and honor and stuff.
How could a man like you
make out good works?
Don't you ever
ask me to invest in your movies!
No!
Help me take care of my mom
and my grandma's seventh brother!
Director Gao!
Didn't you just say to work hard for your dream?
Don't give it up so quickly!
Let me go!
Let me go to die!
Is it meaningful for me to live further?
Movie king.
Come give me a hand!
Let me go. Let me go to die.
Hurry! Or he'll be dead!
Whatever.
Let him jump and be dead.
=Action=
Are you still a human?
Aren't you the caring boy?
How could you look on at this moment?
Don't you have any humanity?
What national star.
I think you're just a cold-blooded animal.
Damn it.
I gave away my true color.
Now I've offended another man.
Fine.
I can remain my investment.
What's more,
I will not
spread this thing around.
What?
Why do you become so kind?
Of course, I don't ask for nothing.
There's a condition.
Condition?
I want you
to sign with me.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪