♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 22=
Are you alright?
Hey! Wait! Wait!
You freak! Put me down! Freak! Freak!
You... You... What are you doing! Freak!
Hush. I can't bear loud voices now.
Was the work that hard?
You haven't even shaved.
My role needs this.
Oh, I see.
I've seen Director Gao's drama.
Your acting has improved a little bit.
You deserve this
since you've paid much effort.
But I still lost the bet.
So, you're accepting that
you can only play villains?
I didn't say that.
It's just I'm not capable enough.
I'm not so mature
about choosing a proper role.
Good. Then let's just
forget about the bet.
In the future,
you can choose the roles as you want.
Really?
You...
You did better than I thought,
this is the reward.
How worse did you think of me?
Actually, I always...
Fall asleep! How can you
fall asleep at such a time!
Finish your words first, okay?
That's so excruciating!
Damn it! Wait and see.
Morning.
Morning. I'm making breakfast.
You can sit there...
What's wrong?
Er... Nothing.
Wait and see.
I forgot to wipe it!
I go clean my face first.
What's wrong?
Breakfast will be done in a minute.
Wait there.
You've to walk a long way to the bathroom.
That's tiring, right?
Are you crazy?
It's mark pens!
Vengeful freak!
How could you scribble on a girl's face!
Okay. Okay. We call it even.
You did it first, okay?
So funny!
You teased me as soon as you came back.
Okay, alright. Was everything alright
when I was not at home?
I wonder if I have the honor to invite you
to sign with our company.
=Mr. Li. Sorry, I've to turn down
your offer of the exclusive contract=
Yes. All going well.
Then I think you can get off me.
I'm a man, you know.
You freak!
Good morning. Jianjian, are you back?
You're back.
Crap.
Why are you eating alone?
What's wrong with your face?
I slapped him. He asked for it himself.
I smell the gossip. I wanna know.
Tell me the details! I want details!
Why you came so early today?
Oh. Lunch. You got a lunch date.
Hey! Su Xiao!
Sis Yan!
I miss you so much.
Me too.
It's a little cold today.
Don't you feel cold?
I'm alright. You know what?
I haven't caught a cold for years.
There is a secret.
Secret? What's that?
Tell yourself that you can't get a cold
since you've piles of jobs to do.
If so...
You won't get a cold.
Seriously?
Definitely won't get a cold.
I've to keep telling myself
"I have no time to get ill,
I can't affect my work".
Then I really won't get a cold.
You're still stubborn.
Oh, I saw the online drama you starred.
Thank you, sis Yan. Thanks.
Li Yan, let's talk about other things.
The role doesn't seem right for you.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪