♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 24=
It's really a super scheming role!
She was the heroine's bestie.
In order to get the trust of the heroine.
She asked someone
to hit against the heroine,
then went to save her.
Really a scheming drama queen. A bitch.
Brother, are you listening to me?
What's that look?
You look so happy.
When you talked about
playing a villain before,
you always looked upset.
How to say it.
Maybe I just figured it out.
Playing a villain also
brings me challenges and experience.
Have you been busy these days?
Not that busy.
I've been studying the script at home.
I can relax myself
coming out with you this time.
Really? I'm relieved then.
I think boss Song
must be satisfied with this role
when he reads the script.
He has been worried about this.
He asked me if you dislike him.
How could that be.
He is very sensitive, you know.
Why he stays at our home every day?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is your Chiffon cake set.
Caramel Macchiato!
I like it the most at this store!
You mentioned this
in your interview last time.
You even know that?
I'm your fan, you know.
Smells so good.
I haven't had this for long.
What's wrong?
Too hot. I accidentally choked.
Peeper.
Brother, I got coffee spilled on me.
I gotta go clean it up.
Something happened.
Hey. Come out.
What are you doing here?
That's my question for you, okay?
Dress like a freak.
Why hanging around here?
No one will recognize me
dressed like this.
Yep. But you may get caught.
Who is that man inside?
He is my...
Didn't I tell you to be careful
and behave yourself?
Ah? What did I do?
Don't you remember
the photo of you dancing with Li Xiwei?
Why should you care?
It's my business where I want to be
and who I wanna be with!
You're with him?
What's wrong?
You've been in a relationship?
When did it start?
Why didn't Sandy tell me that?
What the hell are you bullshitting?
Who on earth is that man!
That sweet smile just now.
They can't just be friends!
Xiaoxiao. What're you doing out there?
He is the man inside with you?
Wai... Wait.
New face. Not an actor or a paparazzo.
He kept following Xiaoxiao,
dressed in such a strange way.
-Who the hell are you?
Easy, you two.
-What is he to you? -What is he to you?
=Sister protector VS Cat keeper=
Brother, he is not a bad guy.
Su Xiao is my sister.
This is my brother, Su Da.
Oh, you're Su Xiao's brother.
I am...
Wait a sec.
Look, they two...
Let get inside first.
You look so weird now.
Go back home first.
Wait...
What? You got snapped by a paparazzo?
You two?
No, three of us.
Who else?
He seems to be
the boss of a brokerage firm.
If you had told me earlier,
I would have greeted him.
But you just neglected me.
What happened then?
He went to get the paparazzo.
What a brisk boss.
See? All deleted.
I admire you.
You even called our chief editor.
Good for you.
Why did you follow Su Xiao?
It has been spread through the circle.
It's said she is after Li Xiwei's heart.
He'll make her popular.
Stay away from her
if you don't wanna get in trouble.
Thank god. Jianjian was with you.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
Those tabloids will make up a story
once they get some photos.
Even your family will get involved.
I lack of such experience.
Later you've to discuss with Sandy
before you wanna do something.
Okay.
=Xiao Jian=
I'll take care of it if anything happens.
Just focus on your drama.
You're capable enough
to play a role vividly.
Help me with the tripod.
Okay. Okay.
You go check this.
Gimme.
The work does not exist
to improve the image of the actor.
While the meaning of an actor is
to improve the quality of the work.
Since you're playing it, do it the best.
I'll exert all my efforts and do it best.
Hello, guys. I'm coming!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪