♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 18=
Oh? She gave that assistant a fright?
Yep. That assistant was
too frightened to speak.
I can imagine that.
However, she's just so softhearted.
Anyhow, be more careful.
Then with the increase of her popularity,
there would be more and more
ill-intentioned people approaching her.
Yep. Real troubles
are ahead waiting for us.
Never mind. She won't be
struck down that easily.
Yixiao!
How did you get hurt so badly!
Sis. Take my head back.
You'll get Shifu's trust.
No, Yixiao, why have to do this?
Finally... I finally...
Finally help you once.
Yixiao, no.
Yixiao!
Cut! Okay. Done.
Sis Yan, this take is done.
No, I won't let go.
Otherwise, you'll finish all your scenes.
Then how can I eat the meals you cook!
You okay, sis Yan?
Just kidding.
You did really well just now.
Well done.
Okay, all confirmed!
Let's congratulate Su Xiao
on finishing her first movie!
Thank you all for your hard work!
Well done!
So nice!
Good job!
Su Xiao, well done.
Good job.
Thank you.
This film is gonna make a hit.
Keep going. I have faith in you.
Thank you, director. Many thanks.
Thank you all for your hard work.
Okay, save these holiday words.
Just enjoy yourselves!
Cheers!
Send this to that guy.
Su Xiao!
Marry me, okay?
Ah. My girl.
Holds her liquor worse and worse.
Oh, no! I wanna be with Xiaoxiao tomorrow!
I wanna eat dishes she cooks!
I know that. I know.
I'll cook you a meal next time, okay?
To be honest,
I've got a lot of help this time.
Thank you, Sandy.
I would never find Yao Mengfang
was behind this without your help.
I wouldn't have found this on my own.
I heard that he was going to
see Xiao Jian.
What the hell are they doing so covertly?
Could it be...
Seems I'm kinda drunk.
Congratulations on finishing your scenes.
It's been so long since I left this place!
So, you've taken here as your home?
No! Not like that!
Remember to contact Jianjian.
What are you talking about?
Er... well, I'm Su Xiao.
=Xiao Jian=
It's about four o'clock
in the afternoon on my side.
It's still night over your side, right?
You can only hear my message
when you get up, right?
Well, I sent you a photo yesterday.
I've finished my first movie successfully.
And... I wanna tell you...
Good luck to your shooting.
This girl...
Not bad.
Su Xiao. Su Xiao.
I fell asleep?
Sorry to wake you up, Su Xiao.
=Invitation: Ms. Su Xiao, hope you can=
=attend the tenth anniversary party...=
=Li Xiwei=
What's this?
An invitation to
Li Xiwei's company's party.
He called me just now.
And delivered it here.
It's said Li Xiwei specially
instructed to invite you.
But two days later, I...
That's right. The schedule is too tight.
Refuse it.
You're here. Welcome.
You're so gorgeous tonight.
Ms. Su Xiao.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪