♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 27=
But I have to work today!
Su Xiao, how about you go there for me?
What?
Sis Yan, I don't think that will do.
How can I be that capable
to take over your job?
And you just suddenly...
Rest easy.
It's just a reality show.
You can totally do it.
A reality show?
Yes, called the Sprint Partners.
Isn't it quite popular lately?
And the guests are all super stars?
Just take it easy.
I've informed the organizer.
It'll be all right.
Yeah, but I...
I feel so dizzy now.
Bye-bye.
Sis Yan, wait, wait, wait.
Su Xiao, I think it could be
a very good opportunity for you.
That makes sense.
But I...
Of course,
you're the one to make the call.
Alright!
It's just to play a game.
Sis Yan finally asked me to help.
Then I can go to give them a reply.
Okay.
Your partner in the program
would be Xiao Jian.
Why him again?!
For this program,
I have to remind you of
something very important.
Because I'm your broker.
So it's not strange for you
to have known Xiao Jian.
Everyone could think of this point.
Brother Wu's side also know it.
Yes.
Nevertheless,
people usually would think
that you two are just boss and employee.
If you get along like
you do at home before cameras,
the audience will
be suspicious of your relations.
It's indeed hard to be explained.
So during the progress of shooting,
you two have to pretend
to be not so familiar.
So it'll also be a test to my acting.
Besides, we just had a fight.
This feels so awkward.
How should I greet him?
Calm down. Calm down.
Time to show my acting skills.
I can do this!
Su Xiao.
Long time no see.
Let's go for it.
Long... Long time no see.
Hi, Xiao Jian and Su Xiao.
I'm Kong Xinyi, this program's director.
It's you two's first time
to join our program?
Hope that it'll be a good cooperation.
Yes, good... good cooperation.
Good cooperation.
Well, I think you must
be unfamiliar to each other?
Yes.
What a coincidence, meet you here again.
Mr. Li is here.
Why is he also here?!
Isn't this Li Xiwei?
Long time no see.
Didn't we just meet each other?
I don't think so.
Did you mistake someone else for me?
Did I?
I don't think my memory is that bad.
I've heard that
your company's business volume
has been increasing lately.
So you're too busy to remember it.
Mr. Xiao, I'm flattered.
You're concerned about my company?
Director, there's something
needs you to confirm.
Oh, coming.
Sorry, I have to go now.
Now you can tell the truth?
Your relationship needs
to be kept a secret?
Because it's her first time
in a variety show.
We don't want some strange topics
to come out of it.
Thank you, Mr. Li.
I see.
So you owe me one this time.
It's so mentally tiring to
take part in a program.
Now, let's begin
our first section of the game!
Barrier Basketball!
The girl in one's team has to
pass through the barriers
with the basketball
and get to the boy under the hoop,
and then give it to the boy
within the required time.
If the boy makes his shot,
they'll get 10 scores.
If the girl sinks a shot directly,
that's 15 scores!
Let's start with
the Blue team of Xiao Jian&Su Xiao.
A national star and
an imposing rising actress!
What kind of performance
will they show us?
Let's wait and see!
So embarrassing.
If it keeps going like this...
I have to...
Congratulate the Blue team,
they're the champion!
Good job, you made this happen.
I'm sorry for what happened last time.
Let's both forget about it.
I have to win!
You'll all know how awesome I am!
Ready?
Su Xiao, pass the ball.
I got this!
Done!
So fast!
Just a blink of an eye,
Su Xiao has completed
the entire game by herself!
They got 15 scores!
No, so horrible.
I'm falling off this...
We're the champion!
The first section ends now.
Xiao Jian and Su Xiao's team
gets a perfect 15-score.
=Blue Team 15, Purple Team 00=
While other two teams
=Green Team 00=
get 0 score due to timeout.
Didn't expect that the gap would
be so huge since the first section.
-What would happen in the game later?
-Let's get together to next task venue!
Please stay with us.
-After the ads... -What do you say?
We'll see it together!
Come with me.
What's wrong?
=No. 8 Warehouse=
What were you doing?
You tried so hard,
thinking you're above anyone else?
Have you ever seen a variety show before?
I... I have.
You've seen how others performed?
How?
They're all so clumsy.
An entertainment show
is made to help people relax.
Those barriers are
set to cause funny effects.
You thought you're in the Olympics?
And you finished the task so fast.
There won't be
a shot of you during the final editing.
I worked hard to finish my job,
anything wrong about that?
You did it wrong.
The purpose of a variety show
is that the audience
find it interesting and funny.
It's not like competitive sports.
Your job is
to entertain the audience
and make them feel happy.
Even if... it's like that,
but we can't...
It should be in this warehouse.
Hurry.
Where is it?
I didn't see it.
So odd. It might be inside there.
Hurry up, or we'll be scolded again.
Yes, it happened last time.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪