♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 28=
They didn't find us,
but this distance is too close.
Pi... Pi...
3.1415926
It's here!
Found it!
...9794...
-Okay, let's bring it back.
-But this is okay, probably?
-...2003... -Are you okay?
...338...
...342117567982148086514382...
...306647093...
-Hey. Hey. -...4607...
...95...
They're already out.
Well, I have to go now.
Well, I'd like to stay here for a while.
What you just said to me,
I got it.
Ready?
Go!
=Blue Team 40, Purple Team 75,
Green Team 60=
Now you're satisfied?
Next, it's swimsuit show.
In the order of
current scores of every team,
the boy shall choose
a swimsuit for the girl first,
and then the girl
puts it on to give a catwalk.
The final scores will be
decided by the mass judges.
Gentlemen,
please go pick out
the nicest for your partner!
Alright.
Time for the last team, the Blue team
with the least scores, go for it!
It's totally a mess here.
Damn it, these are all so ugly!
Alright, next it's the
exciting catwalk show.
So beautiful!
Looks so nice!
The last one.
Let's welcome Su Xiao!
What the hell is this?
And you finished the task so fast.
There won't be a shot of
you during the final editing.
Didn't we agree on more shots?
Since that...
Good, she knows to show her face.
So beautiful!
I see. What a good plan.
Su Xiao is in such good shape.
But the swimsuits prepared are too gaudy.
That'll make her
be judged as vulgar and tasteless.
-But...
-The diving suit not only looks healthy,
but also shows Su Xiao's good shape.
The shock brought by mask off
also shows her cuteness.
What...
The pose you made is so interesting!
Sis, you're so beautiful!
The swimsuit Xiao Jian
chose for you fits you well.
You're best partners.
Thanks. Thank you, everyone.
Next, it's the second half
of today's game.
25-meter freestyle swimming.
Beauties in swimsuit,
time to show your skills!
What's wrong?
I can't swim, actually.
Ah? You...
I thought you could even do triathlon.
I nearly drowned when I was a child, so...
I see. I'll go ask for a waiver.
Don't.
I don't want the show to be boring.
So I'm proved to
have chosen a right swimsuit.
According to the information we just got,
the player Su Xiao can't swim.
But she doesn't want to give up the game.
She asks for a swim ring instead.
Everyone, please cheer her up.
Su Xiao, go for it!
Don't give up!
So shameful.
Everyone, take your marks!
Ready?
Does she do this to me on purpose?
Why I'm still here? Come on!
I won't give up!
This is so hard.
What should I do?
I haven't moved an inch.
-Come on! -Don't give up!
Believe yourself, you can do it!
You performed well.
Go for it, Su Xiao!
Let's go.
Xiao Jian and Su Xiao
arrive at the destination!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪