♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 07=
Okay, Su Xiao.
This scene is about their
reunion after a long time.
Very warm and romantic.
Got it.
Let me show it to you.
Okay.
Wei.
It's really you, Wei.
Sorry.
I won't leave you alone again.
If you do that kind of dangerous thing again,
I will not let you go.
Just like that.
Okay.
I see.
Let's start shooting.
Start.
Ready?
Action!
Wei.
It's really you, Wei.
Sorry.
I won't leave you alone again.
If you
do that kind of dangerous thing again,
I will not let you go.
Cut!
Well done, Su Xiao.
You showed the feelings exactly what I want!
Awesome.She's into it.
Even I get moved.
The show is finished now.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you for your work.
Su Xiao, thank you.
At first, I really didn't know how to do it.
Luckily, you played the heroine.
Director Gao, I'm flattered.
Don't worry.
About the bet you made with Xiao Jian,
you'll definitely win!
If the role that you choose wins,
no matter what kind of role you want to play,
I'll help you get it.
It's all up to you.
However, if the role that I choose wins,
in the future,
you can only play the roles that I choose for you.
Congrats, the movie is done.
Let's dine out to celebrate it.
My brother said that
he'll cook something delicious for me tonight.
Sis Sandy, join me?
How lucky I am.
Brother, I'm back.
Xiaoxiao, you're back.
Your guest?
Brother, this is my new broker, Sis Sandy.
Thank you for taking care of Xiaoxiao.
No... No problem.
It's my duty.
Thank you for taking care of Xiaoxiao.
He's Boss Song, from my brother's company.
He's also my brother's friend.
He often eats with us.
Hi, Boss Song.
So many dishes!
All prepared to congratulate
on the closure of your movie.
Thank you, brother, you're so sweet.
Can we come to eat with you
every time the movie is done?
Feel free to come.
Why it's you to make the promise?
The more people come,
the more natural his visit will be.
Su Xiao...
That's the fact.
Don't say that.
What a good vibe.
I start eating, then.
Go ahead.
So delicious.
Xiaoxiao.
You become thinner again.
Didn't have breakfast well lately?
Because I was shooting day and night lately.
Day and night?
I... I told her to eat, really.
The next movie is coming soon.
I'm afraid that I can't eat well again.
Again?
She will eat well during the shooting.
I... I'll make it arranged.
Sandy.
What?
Do you want to try this?
Oh, yeah.
I'll eat it right now.
Don't be so intimidating.
You scared Sandy.
I just told him to eat more.
Well...
I should
leave now.
I'm killed again.
Here you are.
Look at this.
Nothing has changed.
Xiaoxiao...
Since she had cognition,
she's been upset about her look.
But,
she's actually very cute.
I also think so.
But...
People
all like to judge from appearance.
Xiaoxiao really likes acting.
Of course.
She's very, very hard-working.
She makes progress every day.
We all can see that.
Don't need to be worried.
She'll certainly become
a very excellent actress.
Will she?
Don't tell Xiaoxiao that I'm worried about her.
Relax.
I won't.
Thank you then.
Brother.
Sis Sandy.
Look,
here's the dessert.
Looks yummy.
That's right.
I like making dessert ever since I was a kid.
Xiaoxiao, you worked hard.
And you washed dishes back here
and made the dessert.
I'm finally home.
I should do some house chores.
Thank you, Xiaoxiao.
Keep it up at work.
Xiaoxiao.
I also want a head-touch.
Go away.
Don't be shy.
Not shy, I'm unwilling to do it.
Go away.
Speaking of that...
Don't touch Xiaoxiao.
This aura is really a family trait.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪