♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 05=
A bet?
On what?
Which role that you play is more popular
after the two works get released?
If the role that you choose wins,
no matter what kind of role you want to play,
I'll help you get it.
It's all up to you.
However,
if the role that I choose wins,
in the future,
you can only play the role that I choose for you.
Okay.
Let's make this bet.
You're the Movie King.
You can't go back on your word if you lose.
It seems that it's getting more and more fun.
Su Xiao has such high morale?
So my work will definitely work out.
For this bet,
Su Xiao will surely win!
When we start shooting,
you two,
firstly, get close to each other slowly.
At this distance,
bang!
Switch to No.2 camera at once.
And then,
you look into each other's eyes soulfully.
And then, slowly and slowly,
the camera
gets closer and closer.
And suddenly,
stop!
Okay, it's ready.
It's okay.
I can play it well.
Now feel the scene.
I'm gonna be separated from my love.
Feel it.
Okay, let's shoot it.
Okay, camera on.
Ready?
Action!
I'm really sorry.
Why...
Stop crying.
I can't lose you.
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Su Xiao.
Come check out the playback.
Okay.
Su Xiao.
In this scene, he breaks up with her
in order to keep her safe.
It's a sad scene.
Understood.
I'm really sorry.
Why...
Stop crying.
I can't lose you.
=Congratulation on the heroine=
=The Taste Of Summer
Confidential=
I can make it tomorrow.
Where's Su Xiao?
Still not back?
After a day's shooting,
only a few shots can be used.
Now,
she's being sad in her room.
I knew it.
Jianjian.
How could you know that?
Isn't it obvious?
Jianjian, you're so bad.
Go comfort her.
No need.
I can make it tomorrow.
So confident.
Of course.
I was just too nervous today.
My acting skills are very good.
I used to make it just by one shooting.
Yes.
You're right.
I do steal your man.
It's because you're so useless.
I lied to you.
So what?
Isn't it because you're too stupid?
As long as this old man dies,
his wealth will be mine.
And then...
See?
Very well, right?
That's right
your problem.
Such performance
is like a robot with a set program.
It's not acting.
Just stress response.
What?
That's not stress response!
Listen carefully to Xiao Jian, Xiaoxiao.
You only played one kind of roles for a long time.
So the way of your performance has become rigid.
No matter what you play,
you only have those facial expressions.
Have you really considered the role's mentality?
What kind of person she is?
What is she thinking about?
Why does she say something like that?
Have you ever considered such questions?
To challenge different roles,
it's far from enough by relying
on your previous experience.
Su Xiao.
You just want to be famous
or to be a really excellent actress.
Think it out.
You just want to be famous
or to be a really excellent actress.
Think it out.
=Shudian Film Park=
Hurry up.
You think you're a big star?
You're not afraid of affairs, but I am.
If there're photos about me staying with you,
who knows what kind of news will be released.
Thanks, everyone.
Xiao, why don't you play the hero this time?
I think the leading actor now
is more suitable for that role.
Choosing suitable actors,
is also my responsibility to take as a producer.
Thanks. Thanks.
This freak is so popular.
No wonder he's the movie king.
So many people get cheated by him.
Miss assistant.
Can you pass this gift on to Jian?
Assistant?
Thank you. Please.
But I... I...
And my gift, please give it to him.
Miss assistant.
He's an actor and I'm an actress.
But he's the popular movie king,
I'm taken as an assistant.
What a huge gap!
Little assistant.
We should go now.
Brother Wu.
Xiao Jian.
I should call you boss Xiao.
Don't say that.
I just come to make a visit.
You come here in person.
I'm really flattered.
I'll treat you after the shooting is done.
This is...
Hi, I'm Su Xiao.
I'm also an actress.
Really?
We can work together later if possible.
Okay.
It seems that it's my turn now.
Let's continue shooting if everyone is ready.
I'm leaving then.
We can talk later.
Don't mind us.
Brother Wu has debuted for thirty years.
He's played supporting roles for thirty years.
But,
he's a true actor.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪