♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean♪♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 30=
How about this area?
You're gonna put up
the tents on the beach?
Yes, scenery is so beautiful here.
But is it safe?
For good shooting effects.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
It's so romantic to
sleep over the lapping of waves.
Su Xiao, you're pretty good at this.
When I was still a kid,
I often went camping
with my family in the mountains.
My dad taught me this.
He said that
I'm even more capable than my brother.
So you're quite a quick learner.
No wonder your acting skills are so good.
Ah? I'm flattered, Mr. Xiao.
Done.
I collected so many.
Isn't this enough?
This is a poisonous mushroom.
And this! And this!
Watch it clearly.
This is eatable.
This is poisonous.
They're totally different, okay?
I can't see any difference...
Can't catch one with bare hand.
Is there anything in the tool kit
that can be used as a fishing net?
Did I do anything wrong?
Step away.
Big harvest!
What a monster.
What good partners
Su Xiao and Xiao Jian have made!
They're in harmony so soon.
Su Xiao, don't let the cat out of the bag.
There will be a grand feast!
Su Xiao, you seem to be good at cooking.
Anything that I can help with?
What are you talking about?
Aren't you always
sitting there waiting for food?
You silly cat.
Oops, you've seen that through.
I seldom cook actually.
But I got to mind the manners.
Sure.
I could see it clearly
that you can't cook.
I almost had a heart attack.
Aren't you actually punishing me?
They're performing so well.
It's Su Xiao's first time
in this kind of reality show?
She never joined
any entertainment show before.
So awesome.
Facing that super star Xiao Jian,
she doesn't feel nervous at all.
And it seems that
they're about the same level.
Yes... Yes.
I also feel surprised.
So delicious.
Really? I'm glad that you like it.
I cooked much better than this.
But you never praised me.
What's wrong?
Nothing. This really tastes good.
I'm full.
Didn't expect that I could have
such a good dinner in a desert island.
It's so lucky to be partners with you.
Not really.
He doesn't even blush
saying such ostensible words.
No wonder this freak
could have cheated the nation.
It's raining.
It is.
Su Xiao, let's put these items away.
Okay.
It's getting heavier.
Yes.
Su Xiao, we'd better
go back to the tent first.
In such a program, there will usually be
some man-made troubles
in the next morning.
Let's rest early tonight.
Okay.
It's quite a selling point
to be a good cook.
I think Su Xiao
will definitely be popular.
We'll be waiting for
your program's invitation.
No problem.
Why it rains all of a sudden?
It's not said in the weather forecast.
Go check the latest weather report.
I feel worried now.
Director.
How is that?
Look.
What should we do?
What's up? What happened?
It's said that there
might be a storm at midnight.
Will they get hurt?
But it's just a possibility.
How about waiting for a while?
Director, I don't think this will do.
How about stopping the shooting
and picking them up back here?
But...
There's not but.
Stop the shooting right now.
The biggest concern of our program
should be the
guest players' personal security.
I know you might find it a pity, but...
It'll be too late
if they had any accident.
Indeed, it's too dangerous.
Let's go pick them up now.
The waves are too heavy
that the ship can't sail out.
Su Xiao, Xiao Jian...
The wind is getting heavier.
It's not safe here.
Su Xiao! Get up! Su Xiao!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back♪♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪