♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 26=
What should I do? What should I do?
Oh dear! My sweethearts are both here.
Sandy.
Li Xiwei, you're also here.
What a great feast.
Why didn't you call me here? I hate you.
Didn't I tell you
to stay away from Su Xiao?
Excuse us, Li Xiwei.
We're going to have
a very, very important meeting.
Bye.
Wait a minute.
Hurry, let's go.
See you next time.
Mr. Li, do you want
more dishes as planned?
Keep going.
Why didn't you tell us that
he wants to sign with you?
I didn't want you to be worried.
And I've refused him affirmatively.
Su Xiao.
Don't deal with such things alone next time.
You should let us know first.
Get it?
Oh.
Do you know what kind of a man Li Xiwei is?
You think you can handle him?
How dare you contact him?
I didn't.
He managed to get my phone number.
I just went to refuse him.
You know what,
you shouldn't have been there.
You even ate in front of him.
Why bother deny it?
I didn't mean to dine with him!
But you ate everything up!
Good for you, you dare eat anyone's food.
Don't want to be
a domestic cat but a wild one?
I'm not a cat!
Stupid wild cat.
Freak.
Idiot.
Big freak!
Big idiot!
You two got to stop it right now!
Su Xiao.
Xiao Jian's angry
because he's worried about you.
You understand?
Okay, I get it.
I'll be careful next time.
As long as you can learn from this thing.
Jianjian, stop being mad.
Director Xu just contacted me.
The editing of
Frost Cold As Blood has been done.
I gotta go there now.
You two make peace before I'm back.
Can you do that?
Oh.
Well, I'll be very careful next time.
Made you worried, I'm sorry.
Fine.
No.
Words only can't show your sincerity.
When did you buy all of this?
Which one to use?
This one.
This is not gonna stop, not gonna stop.
Freak will never be short of ways to play.
What's up, kitten?
Let's seize the time to practice.
Don't you always call me kitten!
And you said about the cat movie.
When will it be filmed?
Why did you suddenly bring this up?
I wanted to say this earlier.
I always want to know.
You often make me
wear cat outfits for you.
You said it's for the film.
But I haven't seen the script till now.
Even if I'm stupid,
I'd see the problem, okay?
I'm an independent person.
I have my dignity.
I also need freedom!
Can you just respect me?
Look, you signed the contract all by yourself.
And you agreed to play a cat.
Yes, I agreed to it.
What a bore.
What's wrong with me?
Damn it, couldn't I just talk nicely?
Why?
I can't stop crying.
Su Xiao, morning.
I didn't sleep last night.
What happened?
Not what you expected.
What, so disappointing.
What happened then? Did you make peace?
It's so embarrassing.
I don't want to see him.
Alas, you can't even if you want to.
He didn't tell you that?
A program that he joins starts shooting today.
He's set out and will live in the shooting location.
Is that so?
He's not home.
I feel you two have
a much bigger problem this time.
Alas, what should I do?
Who can come help me?
Oh dear, it's Li Yan.
Hi, what's up? Anything wrong?
Now?
Yes, she's here. What's up?
Didn't you go to the shooting today?
Yes.
Really?
Well, no problem on my side anyway.
Well... Wait. You talk to her directly.
=Li Yan=
Su Xiao, Li Yan has something to tell you.
Me?
Hi, sis Yan, this is Su Xiao.
Su Xiao...
Sis Yan, you... What happened?
I got a fever and now I can't get up.
Forty degree.
Why did you suddenly get a fever?
I didn't go to the hospital,
so it worsened.
Sis Yan, you must go to the hospital.
But I have to work today.
Su Xiao, how about you go there for me?
What?!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪