♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 06=
Wang Yunlong.
People call him Brother Wu.
He was awarded the
Best Supporting Actor of the Gold Crane Award.
And he's been nominated as the
Best Supporting Actor for many major awards.
Camera on!
Ready!
Action!
I've told you everything that I know.
No one else! You have to believe me!
I can swear to god!
You better be honest.
Stop playing such a trick with me.
If you don't tell the truth,
I'll tell my buddies
to take care of your wife and your kid.
I said no one else!
His performance is different from the script.
Should we stop him?
You may beat me to death.
But don't you hurt my wife and my kid?
Old man, why so hysterical?
Want me to beat you?
This old stuff, pretending being dead?
It's really none of their business!
I did that alone! I did that alone!
Cut!
Okay!
Brother Wu, are you alright?
No big deal, I'm fine.
Director, it was kind of impromptu.
Will that do?
If not, I can do it again.
No need.
It's pretty good.
Right to the point.
Brother Wu.
Your acting also made me excited.
Did I use too much strength?
It's okay. It's okay.
If not, how can there be the effect?
But,
it depends on the director's consideration.
For a good actor,
whether he's the leading
role or the supporting role,
that he gets to the role's inner world
matters the most.
That question again.
You want to be famous
or to be an excellent actress?
I...
I want...
Please come in.
Sis Sandy.
Xiao Jian called.
The shooting is delayed.
So he'll come back tomorrow morning.
He'll not have supper with us.
Got it.
I've heard that.
You saw Brother Wu today.
Didn't you?
Any thought?
I feel so ashamed.
Brother  Wu's acting is so good.
And I kind of figure out
why that freak could be a big star.
Can I also be like them?
No one was born as a big star.
Neither was Xiao Jian.
Cut.
Okay.
Good job.
You acted well.
Isn't it?
I think I've made huge progress.
Brother Jian.
Next scene is,
you meet your dad on the other
side of the playground,
and then you two have a fight.
The actor asks if you and  director
can rehearse it again?
What do you say?
No need.
It's unnecessary.
I've remembered the lines.
Brother Jian.
Will you join the gathering next time?
On which day?
If I'm free...
You're Xiao Jian?
Hello. Hello.
I'm Wang Yunlong.
In this scene,
I play the father.
After the shooting that day,
Jianjian changed, as if he's another man.
He told me
after going through that scene,
it's like he couldn't act any more.
Later, he watched that show
for dozens of times.
He asked, Sis Sandy,
am I still too inexperienced?
Really?
To be honest,
I was also given a blow.
Although Xiao Jian was very popular,
when we saw Brother Wu's acting,
we felt like that
we can't be self-complacent.
There's still a long way to go.
So from then on,
we've kept working hard
and make it to today.
After saying so much, I become hungry.
You're also tired, right?
Don't cook then.
I'll call food delivery.
Let me know if you want to eat something.
Sis Sandy.
Thank you.
Just a food delivery.
Don't need to be so grateful.
I want...
To be an excellent actress.
I'm gonna be an excellent actress.
Is he dead?
Alive.
But his eye circles are so dark.
It's a chance to take revenge.
Aren't you somebody?
Movie King.
Big star.
Aren't you ferocious?
Sharp tongue. Freak.
It seems that he's been tired from work.
He took time to take me to see Brother Wu.
I'll become a good actress for you.
So,
next,
as a reward,
let me poke into your nose.
What?
You're in such a hurry
to perform our contract?
You...
What are you talking about?
Let me go.
Think about the contract,
and then you'll know what you should do.
First of all,
have breakfast.
Come. Come.
This way. This way.
Say meow. Say meow.
Look. Look.
No one was born as a big star.
But someone was born as a freak.
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪