♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 32=
Why are we fighting again?
It's not appropriate to be
at odds with her right now.
I'd better...
Well, just now...
Don't cross the line, you freak.
You...
You're a pupil?
Why did you draw a line?
You're the naive pupil!
You freak...
That's so scaring.
Sorry, I...
We'll get warm faster
if hugging each other.
Are you still upset about
your look?
Much less than before.
Sis Yan said my eyes make me an actress.
I also like your eyes.
I also told Sandy about it.
Actually I noticed
you a very long time ago.
Although your acting skills
are not mature,
your eyes are firm and sharp.
It'd be a pity if you get ignored.
So Sandy actually
kept watching you for me.
Then those things happened.
Well, what I am now,
is it the same as you imagined?
You think I would be wrong?
You're much better than I imagined.
You're more like a cat than I imagined!
Shut up! Or I'll scratch your face!
Although it's kinda like
lines in some vulgar romance drama,
we do have been through
many things together.
Yes, we have.
Let's make a bet
on the two roles.
You just want to be famous?
Or you want to be an excellent actress?
Think it over.
You performed much better than I thought.
This is your reward.
So, everything has been arranged by you.
No, it's our kismet predetermined by God.
Our lines are getting more vulgar.
Yes, vulgar.
Do you want something more vulgar?
Okay.
Well, just now...
Well, it's...
Yes, it's...
Acting practice.
Morning.
You slept well?
Yes.
Xiao Jian!
Su Xiao!
It's so good to see you being safe.
I was so worried.
Don't worry, I'm not that weak.
Director Gao.
Why are you here?
He rushed here the minute
the storm stopped.
He even left his film behind,
to be finished editing.
Director Gao.
Su Xiao.
Thank you!
Isn't it a matter of course?
You're the most important friend to me!
It's good that everyone is all right.
Sorry, we made you worried.
How is the shooting equipment?
Most of the equipment are broken.
You two were off the camera
ever since the storm.
What a pity.
You two's relationship
didn't get to the X-rated?
What do you mean by that?
My offence. Forget about it.
Jianjian.
Let's go.
It's not good to your skin
basking under the sun.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Um.
What should I do?
I don't know
how to get along with him
naturally in the future.
Xiaoxiao!
Come up or I won't take you with us!
Wait, Sandy!
Xiaoxiao.
You suffered a lot.
Sandy said that
it's so dangerous this time.
It's kinda a rare experience.
I'm gonna reward you with this big feast!
Su Xiao, you're so awesome.
I'm gonna keep this episode for good.
The diving suit is
quite suitable for you, Xiaoxiao.
Indeed. It's because she's in good shape.
Cut. Cut. Cut.
What's wrong?
Anything wrong about my acting?
Your emotion is not right.
It's far away from
the asked scenario requirements.
Liu Xuxu is not in a good mood today.
She's just like this.
Su Xiao!
Another new film
named you to be the heroine.
You got the role totally
by your real strength.
So great.
What's more, the film about cats
that Xiao Jian planned
has been passed officially.
You should also get prepared.
Sorry.
I misunderstood you before.
Thanks for your help
during this period of time.
Thank you.
Words are just words.
Not sincere enough.
Well, let's continue
our practice from now!
Look. Look.
We got so many new tails!
What do you say? Isn't it nice?
Do you like it?
Xiao Jian, you freak!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don’t you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin cart of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat ♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪