♪One, move into the role in a second♪
♪And two, gather all your vitality together♪
♪Freeze, aggressiveness showed by eye contact♪
♪Take your own position♪
♪Your eyes, I won't waver♪
♪Your smile, save it♪
♪Hey, what exactly does that mean?♪
♪I'm confused♪
♪Pushing my luck to deal with all♪
♪Yet my desire deep down has nowhere to hide♪
♪The ideal relationship should be in one take♪
♪Take a deep breath♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, stride forward♪
♪Take two, shake shoulders♪
♪That courage drives you crazy♪
♪Flexible fingers beating♪
♪Draw an arc♪
♪The meaning of magic♪
♪Let me prove it♪
♪Oh oh oh♪
♪Take one, keep a distance♪
♪Take two, infinitely getting close♪
♪I can hardly breathe♪
♪The secret deep in the island♪
♪The unknown plot♪
♪See breeze on a summer night♪
♪Arouses the aura of danger♪
=Spicy Girl=
=Episode 13=
Xiaoxiao, wait for me here. I go check in.
Thanks, Sis Sandy.
What the hell is this hotel!
And you let me live in that fucking standard room!
Do you know who I am?
That's...
But deluxe suits are for starring roles.
Liu Xuxu...
Cut off this shit! I can't live in such a room anyway!
How could she behave like this?
I have an investor at my back!
Do you wanna get fired?
I'm back.
Ms. Liu, we really can't help with this.
What a good place it is!
Never thought we could live in such a nice hotel
shooting on location in the suburbs.
Of course. After all, it's a big-budget movie.
Yes. If someone is still fastidious
staying in such a nice hotel,
why not just back home and play house?
Su Xiao!
Ah, Liu Xuxu, it's you.
Are you in a meeting?
None of your business.
Hey! Gimme the room key.
Okay.
Many thanks.
It's okay. This hotel is indeed nice.
It does look good.
But the rooms are not well insulated.
Ah? I see.
Why my room is next to hers! Pisses me off!
I gotta ask Li Xiwei to change another
room for me when he comes!
What fucking hotel and crew!
How come the director chose her!
Well... Indeed not well insulated.
Damn it!
Wow! What a beautiful shooting location!
Such fresh air.
It'll be a while before the shooting starts.
Do you wanna put up makeup first?
I'd like to stay here for a while.
All right. Enjoy the scenery here,
and get some feel.
I go get ready with the crew, see you later.
It's so quiet that I could only
hear the rustle of leaves.
It's rare to be away from the noisy city.
Xiaoxiao!
It's amazing. The rustle even made me feel like
someone is calling my name.
Xiaoxiao!
Really sounds like that.
Could it be the fairies of the forest?
Xiaoxiao!
Wait. There's really someone calling me.
It's me! Xiaoxiao!
I've been waiting for you, Xiaoxiao!
Director Gao!
Director Gao, I didn't expect you're also here.
We're sent to find a view in advance.
We've been waiting for you here.
That's so good!
Seeing me makes you that happy?
Or do you want me to take advantage of you?
Go to hell!
Just kidding.
I don't wanna hear such kidding.
Xiao Jian is on your side now. How dare I do that?
Speaking of this, but for me,
how would you have met Xiao Jian.
Exactly.
I heard from Senior Xu that you did a good job.
Seems that being with the movie king does help.
You got improved in acting.
I'm not with him!
Then, what's relationship between you?
Yes... What's our relationship?
Only interests matter between us.
But, why my heart...
Ms. Su, your skin looks so good.
No one has praised me that.
I've been your fan since I saw your last scene.
I'm so lucky to do your makeup.
Ah? Fan? I had no fans before.
Well, I'll be your number-one fan then.
My name is Yao Mengfang.
Okay, ready!
Action!
Go straight along this road and you'll get out.
Sis, why don't you leave with me?
I still got things to do. Don't worry about me. Now go.
Just give it up!
You thought it's so east to run away?
I didn't expect you two are in cahoots.
Yixiao, run!
I promised I would protect her as long as I could!
Cut! Okay.
Thank you for your guidance.
You're so good at acting at such young age.
Very promising.
No, no, I'm flattered.
You must have learnt a lot, right?
Recently, I did find myself many shortcomings,
so when I went back...
Went back?
With the guidance from me,
such a national movie king.
And thanks to me, you can be in this movie.
So when you come back, you've to...
Act as a cat.
A cat? You mean liberating nature? That's basic.
Forget what I said, please!
Er... Okay.
Thank you so much!
What are you bullshitting?
Not that!
-Sorry, we gotta go.
-Let me explain it, Sis Sandy!
She is really cute.
You're right.
I didn't say anything! I mean it!
♪Like a zero-degree coke without carbohydrate♪
♪Lying on the ten-centimeter mattress♪
♪Refreshing mobile text messages♪
♪Being a lazy cat that only belongs to you♪
♪Why don't you still not answer me back?♪
♪Stretch myself♪
♪Walk quietly♪
♪The pumpkin carriage of midnight
please come later♪
♪Just let me be immersed♪
♪In your gentle hug♪
♪Because my heartbeat♪
♪Has sounded the alarm of coma♪
♪I love you♪